--==本影片由 CMCT 团队荣誉出品==--
更多精彩影视 请登陆 http://cmct.cc/
影片压制: 暮雨潇潇   字幕制作：十三少   招募Q号: 76846146
纽约《预言家》报载 1911年11月26日
In The New York Herald, November 26, year 1911...
三名死囚被执行绞刑
...there is an account of the hanging of three men.
他们被指控谋杀了埃德蒙・威廉姆・戈弗雷爵士
They died for the murder of Sir Edmund William Godfrey...
一个优秀的丈夫 父亲 药商
...husband, father, pharmacist, and all-around gentleman resident...
伦敦格贝希区的优秀市民
...of Greenberry Hill, London.
而这三个游民杀死他的唯一动机 仅仅是为了抢劫
He was murdered by three vagrants whose motive was simple robbery.
他们分别是约瑟夫・格林
They were identified as Joseph Green...
斯坦利・贝里
...Stanley Berry...
丹尼尔・希尔
...and Daniel Hill.
格林 贝里 希尔
Green, Berry, Hill.
嗯 但愿这只是一个巧合
And I would like to think this was only a matter of chance.
里诺报报道 1983年6月
As reported in the Reno Gazette, June of 1983...
发生了一场火灾
...there is the story of a fire...
在泼下的灭火的水中发现了一具尸体
...the water that it took to contain the fire...
他叫德尔默・达里恩 是一名潜水爱好者
...and a scuba diver named Delmer Darion.
他在内华达州里诺市的金块旅馆及赌场工作
Employee of the Nugget Hotel and Casino, Reno, Nevada...
是二十一点的发牌手 然而真正让德尔默痴迷的是
...engaged as a blackjack dealer, well-liked and well-regarded...
在湖中潜水
...as a physical, recreational, and sporting sort...
这才是他喜爱的运动
...Delmer's true passion was for the lake.
根据验尸官的报告 德尔默因心脏病突发
As reported by the coroner, Delmer died of a heart attack...
死在湖与树林之间的某个地方
...somewhere between the lake and the tree...
是另外一件事情引起了人们的好奇 事发第二天 一名叫做克雷格・汉森的人自杀了
...but most curious side note is the suicide the next day of Craig Hansen...
他是志愿的救火员 当时他抛下自己可怜的四个孩子
...volunteer firefighter, estranged father of four...
正在酗酒 汉森是飞行员
...and a poor tendency to drink. Mr. Hansen was the pilot of the plane...
他的飞机匪夷所思地将德尔默・达里恩舀了起来
...that quite accidentally lifted Delmer Darion out of the water.
更加偶然的是 汉森在两天前的晚上
Added to this, Mr. Hansen's tortured life...
曾经和德尔默・达里恩打过交道
...met before with Delmer Darion just two nights previous.
我再要个2
All I need is a two.
你想要个两点 好吧
All you need is a deuce. All right.
这是个8
That is an eight.
没办法 这就是现实
Glad you like my work. All right. Moment of truth-
他的负罪感如此之强 如此之大 以致于
The weight of the guilt and the measure of coincidence so large...
克雷格・汉森因此选择了自杀
...Craig Hansen took his life.
对此 我无论如何 还是仅仅想将它看作是一个巧合
And I am trying to think this was all only a matter of chance.
1961年美国法医鉴定协会的颁奖晚宴上
The tale told at a 1961 awards dinner...
协会主席约翰・哈勃
...for the American Association of Forensic Science...
讲述了这样一个故事
...by Dr. John Harper, president of the association...
一个简单的企图自杀的故事
...began with a simple suicide attempt.
很惊奇吧
curiosity.
一个叫做希尼・巴林杰的十七岁男孩
Seventeen-year-old Sydney Barringer...
发生在洛杉矶市 1958年3月23号
...in the city of Los Angeles on March 23rd, 1958.
据验尸官事后说 这桩本不会成功的自杀
The coroner ruled that the unsuccessful suicide...
在一瞬间不幸地成功地变成一桩谋杀
...had suddenly become a successful homicide.
首先这本应是一桩自杀
To explain, the suicide was confirmed by a note...
证据是来自希尼・巴林杰口袋中的小纸条
...in the right hip pocket of Sydney Barringer.
就在小希尼站在楼台上同时
At the same time young Sydney stood on the ledge of this nine-story building...
三层以下正在爆发一场争吵
...an argument swelled three stories below.
当时邻居们都听见 这对房客夫妇又像往常一样吵架
The neighbors heard, as they usually did, the arguing of the tenants...
并且也像往常一样 手持猎枪威吓另外一个
...and it was not uncommon for them to threaten each other with a shotgun...
当然有时也会用手枪
...or one of the many handguns in the house.
我要打死你
I'm gonna put you down!
然而当她无意中抠下猎枪扳机时
And when the shotgun accidentally went off...
畜牲
You asshole!
希尼正巧掉了下来
Sydney just happened to pass.
什么?
What?
别他妈说话!
Shut the fuck up!
更巧的还在后面
Added to this, the two tenants turned out to be...
这两位房客分别是费伊和亚瑟・巴林杰
...Faye and Arthur Barringer...
希尼的父亲和母亲
...Sydney's mother and Sydney's father.
面对起诉
When confronted with the charge...
警方描述事情经过时
...which took some figuring out for the officers on the scene of the crime...
费伊・巴林杰发誓自己根本不知道猎枪里有子弹
...Faye Barringer swore she did not know the gun was loaded.
我不知道
I didn't know.
她经常这样威胁我 所以我从来不上子弹
She always threatens me with the gun, but I don't keep it loaded.
你从来不上子弹吗?
DETECTlVE: And you didn't load the gun?
我怎么可能上子弹哪?
Why would I load the gun?
一个住在这座楼里的
A boy who lived in the building...
经常和希尼・巴林杰在一起玩的小男孩
...sometimes a visitor and friend to Sydney Barringer...
告诉警方 他在六天前曾经看到 这把枪上了子弹
...said that he had seen, six days prior, the loading of the shotgun.
里基 过来一下
Ricky, come here a minute.
能看得出 这种无休止的争吵与厮打
lt seems that all the arguing and fighting...
无休止的家庭暴力 给希尼・巴林杰造成很大心理伤害
...and all of the violence was far too much for Sydney Barringer...
他知道父母还会继续下去
...and knowing his mother and father's tendency to fight...
于是他决定做些什么
...he decided to do something.
他说他想让他们杀了对方
He said that he wanted them to kill each other...
他们这么吵本来就是想杀了对方
...and that's all that they wanted to do, kill each other...
所以他就帮助他爸妈这么做啦
...and that he would help them do that if that's what they wanted.
希尼・巴林杰从九楼屋顶跳下
Sydney Barringer jumps from the ninth-floor rooftop.
他的父母正在六楼吵架
His parents argue three stories below.
母亲无意中按下扳机 正好打穿了希尼胃部
Her accidental shotgun blast hits Sydney in the stomach...
就在他掉落经过六楼窗户时
...as he passes the arguing sixth-floor window.
当场就被打死了 但他继续往下掉
He is killed instantly, but continues to fall...
然而就在二楼 有一个三天前装上的安全网
...only to find, five stories below, a safety net installed three days prior...
这个用来保护洗窗工人的网子 本可以截住救了他
...for window washers that would've broken his fall...
当然如果他胃上没被打出那个大洞的话
...and saved his life if not for the hole in his stomach.
他的母亲费伊・巴林杰被指控谋杀
So Faye Barringer was charged with the murder of her son...
小男孩自己则被控对自己的死 犯有协同罪
...and Sydney Barringer noted as an accomplice in his own death.
发言人简单地评述为
And it is in the humble opinion of this narrator...
这不是件普普通通的事儿
...that this is not just something that happened.
不是那种每时每刻发生着的事儿
This cannot be one of those things.
这事儿 拜托 当然和它们不同
This, please, cannot be that.
我想说 我不只这么认为
And for what I would like to say, I can't.
这不能简单地归于巧合
This was not just a matter of chance. Ha, ha.
而且这种听起来邪门的事 其实从来没有停止过
These strange things happen all the time.
在这个巨大的游戏中
ln this big game that we play, life, it's not what you hope for.
你的人生不会因为你的希望和等待而改变 你必须付诸于行动
It's not what you deserve. It's what you take.
我是弗兰克・T・J ・麦吉
I'm Frank T.J. Mackey, a master of the muffin...
《诱惑与征服》的作者
...and author of Seduce and Destroy...
现在录音带和录像带已经全套上市
...now available to you on audio and video cassette.
《诱惑与征服》将传授给你无以伦比的技巧
Seduce and Destroy will teach you the techniques...
让那些火爆的金发女郎
...to have any hard-body blonde...
为你倾倒 为你疯狂
...just dripping to wet your dock.
我们需要什么? 仅仅是语言
Bottom line? Language:
这是揭开女性底层心理的密匙
the magical key to unlocking the female analytical mindset.
直接抓住她的思想
Tap directly into her hopes, her wants...
她的恐惧 她的欲望 和她那条可爱的小衬裤
...her fears, her desires, and her sweet little panties.
迅速掌握如何让她成为你的伙伴 成为为你所饥渴燃烧的性奴
Learn how to make that lady friend your sex-starved servant.
《诱惑与征服》 你可以学成再付费
Seduce and Destroy produces an instant, money-back guaranteed...
你将进入那种令女人们迷醉的状态
...trance-like state that will get you...
嘿
Hey.
你将不费吹灰之力得征服她们
naughty sauce you want fast.
你还能忍受多少次
Hey, how many more times...
听到那句无法忍受的回答
...do you need to hear the all-too-famous line-
那么
So?
我真的对你没有感觉
I just don't feel that way about you?
三十多年间 无数美国人收看
DlCK For over 30 years, America has hung out...
并参与吉米・加托的问答节目
...and answered questions with Jimmy Gator.
他已经成为美国电视的一个传奇
An American legend and a true television icon...
这个星期 吉米将庆祝他广播生涯的第12000小时
...Jimmy celebrates his 12,000th hour of broadcast this week.
我真的已经工作那么久了吗?
Have I been around that long?
他是一位结婚四十年的爱家男人
DlCK He's a family man who's been married for over 40 years...
有两个孩子 还有一个即将出生的孙子
...with two children and one bouncing baby grandchild on the way.
我们已经习惯每天收看
We've tuned in each day to see the human interaction...
吉米与那些超常孩子们的智慧的交流
...between Jimmy and some very special kids...
我们还希望这种三十年的精彩能够继续下去
...and we hope there's 30 more years of watching that happen.
我是吉米・加托
I'm Jimmy Gator.
答案是唐纳德・W・温尼科特 1911年 北美洲 南美洲
Donald W. Winnicott. 1911. North America. South America.
答案是4 答案是22 地心引力
The answer is four. The answer is 22. Gravity.
答案是塞缪尔・约翰逊的一生
The answer is The Life of Samuel Johnson.
我不在乎你的银行账单
I don't care what your last bank statement is.
快走吧 本来你十分钟前就该好了
Let's go. You should have done that 10 minutes ago.
-我们还要多带些狗食 -先上车再说
-We need more dog food. -RlCK: Talk in the car.
- 听着 今天我有重要工作 - 你孤单吗?
- Look, I got a serious audition today. - Are you lonely?
- 这个也要拿是吧? - 我需要这个
- RlCK: That one too? - I need this one.
好 让我来告诉你
Well, let me tell you.
真不明白你干嘛要带上四袋子书去上学
RlCK: I don't understand why you need four bags of books to go to school.
没有理由带这么多背包
There's no reason for this many backpacks.
- 两点我接你 - 应该是一点半
- Be ready at 2:00. - lt should be 1:30.
- 我跟你讲过了我今天工作很紧 - 只能两点赶到了
- RlCK: I told you I got an audition. - I won't be here till 2:00.
快 拿好你这堆东西 我得走了 我爱你
Get your stuff. Come on. Gotta go. Love you.
- 我也爱你 - 好
- Love you too. - Okay.
丹尼尔 你有答案了吗?
Donnie, do you have an answer?
有了 吉米 答案是普罗米修斯
I do, Jimmy. Prometheus.
答对了
JlMMY: lt is!
丹尼尔 感觉怎么样?
Donnie, how does it feel?
我很激动 我保证象我这个年纪的来装牙箍的肯定不多吧
lt's pretty exciting. Bet you don't get many people my age getting braces.
你当时在那个比赛里好可爱
You were so cute on that game show.
但我敢说你现在都回答不上来了吧!
Bet you can't answer any questions now, though, huh? Ha, ha!
- 丹尼尔一切正常 - 很好
- So we're all set to go, Donnie. - DONNlE: Good.
- 明早见 - 好
- I'll see you tomorrow morning. - Okay.
- 再见 - 你也太忙了吧?
- RECEPTlONlST: Bye. - You're running around like crazy.
马上就迟到啦
I'm gonna be late for work.
嘿
Hey.
是神童丹尼尔・史密斯
lt's the Quiz Kid, Donnie Smith.
你好 你好
PHlL: Hello, hello.
- 今天感觉如何? - 遭透了
- How's today, then? - Fucking bullshit is what this is.
悔恨
EARL：Fucking regrets
为我这一生做过的事情悔恨
And we do these things, move through this life.
我需要你的帮助 菲尔 今天你得帮我点忙
I'm gonna need your help, Phil. You got to help me on something today.
尽管说 厄尔 什么事都行的
I'll take care. Anything, Earl.
为什么 因为你是他的医生 这就是为什么!
Well, you're his doctor, and that's why.
告诉我 告诉我
Tell me something. Tell me something.
他需要更大的剂量!
He needs more pills. He needs more- Fuck it.
他需要吃更多的药 而我需要知道病情的真相
He needs more pills, and I need some answers...
我马上就过去见你
...so I'm coming to see you.
早上好 琳达
Morning, Linda.
我爱你 亲爱的
I love you, my darling.
我马上就回来 有点事情我必须解决
I'll be back in a while, Phil. I have to do some things...
我得去弄清楚 马上回来
...and I have to see something, and I'll be back.
妈的!
Fuck.
我靠 他妈的
Fuck, fuck, fuck.
按1键收听
WOMAN Press one to hear...
每一位的自我简介
...this person's personal description of themselves...
按下2键可以给他留言
...and two to leave a personal message of your own.
嗯 你好 我是吉姆 我负责维护法律的实施
JlM Well, hello. This is Jim. I work in law enforcement.
事实上我是洛杉矶警局的警察
I'm an officer for the LAPD...
在北好莱坞街区负责巡逻
...and work out of the North Hollywood district.
我喜欢我的工作 也喜欢上电影
I love my job, and I love to go to the movies.
我尝试让自己保持身体健壮 因为工作需要一个这样的我
I try to stay physically fit. My job demands it.
所以我的身材很棒 但是近来在慢慢变胖
I'm getting up there, though.
我今年32岁 6英尺2英寸 体重大概是 180磅吧
I'm 32 years old, and I'm 6'2 tall, and I weigh about 180...
如果你十分在意的话
...if that's important to you.
我很希望能认识特别点的女孩 她最好喜欢安静
I'm really interested in meeting someone special who likes quiet things.
我的生活压力很大 所以希望能和她保持一种平稳沉静的
My life is very stressful, and I hope to have a relationship that is very calm...
互相关爱 不一味奢求回报的关系
...and undemanding and loving...
如果你是这样的女孩 请给我留言 我的语音信箱号是 8- 2
...so if you are this person, please leave me a message at box number 82.
谢谢
Thank you.
暴力如此猖獗
OFFlCER: So much violence...
但这就是我们的社会 总之还是祝你们好运
...but that's the way of the world. Good luck, as always.
祝你们一如既往地坐在车里 平平安安地执行任务
Serve and protect and all that other blah, blah, blah on the side of the car.
你听我说
JlM: Let me tell you something.
这不是什么轻松的工作
This is not an easy job.
首先我从接收器里收到中心的信息
I get a call on the radio from Dispatch.
一般是个坏消息
lt's bad news.
坏得发臭
And it stinks.
但这就是我的工作 不管怎样 我喜欢它
But this is my job, and I love it...
因为我想做得更好些
...because I wanna do well.
我想在这一生中 在这个世界上 我能努力做好我的事
ln this life and in this world, I wanna do well...
我想帮助别人
...and I wanna help people.
虽然我可能一天会接到20个这样的坏消息
And I might get 20 bad calls a day...
但总会让我抓住一次来帮助别人 救一个人
...but one time I can help someone, I make a save...
纠正一次错误 或者及时控制局面
... I correct a wrong or right a situation...
都能让我变成快乐的巡警
...then I'm a happy cop.
在这一生中 我们要尽量做些好事
And we move through this life, we should try and do good.
做善事
Do good.
如果我们能做到这一点
And if we can do that...
并且没有伤害到其他人的话
...and not hurt anyone else...
那么
...well, then....
- 嘿? - 谁啊? 事儿怎么那么多!
JlM: Hello? MARClE: I turn around, there's something.
- 放轻松 - 你怎么能随便闯进来!
- Whoa! Slow down. - You can't just come in here.
女士 门是开着的 我接到举报
- The door was open. - You not allowed to come in.
- 不许进来! - 冷静些
- Calm down. - I am calm!
我很冷静 我接到举报 说这间屋子里非常吵闹
I got a call to this apartment, report of a disturbance.
这间屋子里从来没有人吵闹过
There's no disturbance.
我接到了扰民的举报 门开着 所以我不得不进来看看到底发生了什么
I got a call of a disturbance. I wanna see what's going on.
这里没有吵闹! 没吵闹你紧张什么呢!
- Yeah, but there's no disturbance. - Then you got nothing to worry about.
因为你刚才没说 我清楚自己有什么权利 你不能
You don't tell me. I know my rights. Just come right in. You can't just....
哦 女士你想测试我是么?
All right, ma'am, you wanna test me?
如果你想考我法律那么现在就可以开始
All right? You wanna tell me about the law book, we can do that.
如果你再推我的话我可以把你关进去
You push me far enough, I will take you to jail.
- 现在 冷静下来! - 我 非常 冷静!
- Okay? Now calm yourself down. - I am calm!
你一点都不冷静 因为你正在冲我大喊大叫
No. You are not calm. You're screaming at me.
明白了么?
Do you understand?
我接到一个扰民的举报 现在我要调查一下
I got a call of a disturbance, and I'm going to check it out.
所以我要开始调查了
That is what I'm going to do.
你一个人住这儿? 我不需要回答你!
- Are you alone in here? - I ain't got to answer your questions.
你可以不回答 但是我还是会再问你一遍
No, you don't, but I'm gonna ask you one more time.
你一个人住这儿么? 你自己觉着呢?
- Are you alone in here? - What does it look like?
- 没有其他人在这里是吧? - 你在
- There's no one else in here? - You in here.
没错 那么没有其他人
Okay. That's true, but is there anyone else...
除了你我之外的其他人在这里么?
...besides me and besides you in this house?
我已经说过了 没有!
- No. I said that already. - Mm- hm.
- 你是不是在说谎? - 我是一个人住的
- Are you lying to me? - I live by myself.
这倒可能是真的 但我现在的问题是
That might be true, but the question I'm asking you, ma'am....
现在这个房子里还有没有其他的人?
ls there anyone else in this house right now?
- 没有 - 好吧
- No. - Okay.
- 你叫什么? - 玛茜
- What is your name? - Marcie.
玛茜 你最好坐下
Okay. Marcie, I'm gonna need you to take a seat here.
- 我喜欢站着 - 我不是请求你 坐下
- I prefer to stand up. - Okay. I'm not asking.
- 我什么都没有做! - 快去坐下 女士!
- I didn't even do nothing. - Move, ma'am.
好吧 我要开始检查了
Okay. So, like I was saying, I'm here to check on a disturbance.
你的邻居们举报说听到尖叫声和一声巨响
Now, some of your neighbors heard screaming and a loud crash.
- 我从来没听到什么巨响! - 好 那是 ?
- I don't even know no loud crash. - Okay, what- ?
- 什么声音? - 我什么都没听见
- What was that? - Nothing.
在椅子上坐好 我什么都没做
- Sit back down on the couch. - I ain't gotta do a goddamn thing.
- 你他妈的要干什么? - 别这样
- What's this bullshit? - Do not do this.
- 别打我 女士 - 混蛋 胡扯
- Do not do this. Do not slap me, ma'am. - This is bullshit. This is bullshit.
干什么!啊?你想干什么!
This is bullshit. For what? For what? For what? Huh? Tell me for what.
不 你干什么?
No, tell me for what.
我要求你坐在椅子上 坐好
JlM: I asked you to sit on the couch. MARClE: This is bullshit.
胡扯 他妈的胡扯
This is bullshit. This is fucking bullshit.
我需要支援
15- L- 27, I'm gonna need backup.
你他妈的要干什么? 你个狗东西!
What the fuck is this? lt's bullshit, motherfucker!
别过来 马克尔 你他妈的 什么都没有!
- I want you to stay right there. - Fucking bullshit, and you know it!
- 在那儿呆着 马克尔 - 不许进我的卧室!
JlM: Stay right there, Marcie. - Don't you go in my bedroom!
你他妈的!混账东西! 别进走廊!
This is bullshit, motherfucker! Don't go down the hallway!
不许往前走了 别他妈的往前走了!
Don't go down my motherfucking hallway!
洛杉矶警察!
JlM: This is the LAPD!
别他妈进我卧室!
Don't go in my goddamn bedroom!
举双手出来!
JlM: Come out now with your hands up!
听见没有?! 那儿什么都没有!
MARClE: What did I tell you? Ain't nobody in there!
你还往哪儿走 狗东西?!
Where the fuck you going, motherfucker?
别他妈进我卧室!
Don't go in my goddamn bedroom!
离我的壁橱远点!你他妈的!
Stay out of my motherfucking closet! What did I tell you?
你他妈听见没!? 我是警察!
- Don't go down my hallway! - This is the police!
壁橱里有人吗? 出来
lf there is anyone in this closet, come out...
让我看到你的双手
...and show yourself to me now, with your hands up.
玛茜 别再拖椅子了!
Marcie, do not drag that couch any further!
别藏着了!
Don't do this, ma'am!
我壁橱里什么都他妈的没有!
There's nobody in my motherfucking closet!
我要打开壁橱 我会开枪的!
lf I have to open this closet, you will get shot!
快回来 你他妈的混蛋!
MARClE: Come back here! Come back here, motherfucker!
我他妈的有话和你说!
What can't you goddamn fucking talk to me?
那里面什么人都没有! 我告诉你! 马克尔 闭嘴!
- There's nobody in there! I told you! JlM: Marcie, quiet down!
你他妈的别乱来了! 净他妈胡来!混蛋!
MARClE: This don't make no fucking sense! This don't make no goddamn sense!
你妈的!狗东西!
This is bullshit, motherfucker!
过来问我!为什么不过来问我!?
Why can't you talk to me?
哇哦 喔
Whoa! Whoa- ho!
这他妈是什么啊?玛茜
What the hell is this, Marcie?
那不是我的
That ain't mine.
我们坐在这儿时他正在慢慢死去
LlNDA: He's dying. He's fucking dying as we're sitting here.
竟然他妈的连个办法都
There's not a fucking...
天哪!你怎么能叫我冷静下来!?
Jesus, how can you tell me to calm down?
我能做的就是尽我所能帮助你
I can help you through this, but there's certain things...
但你也知道的 你必须接受这个事实 我们可以接受它的
...you're gonna have to take care of, and we can go over them...
不过前提是你必须安静坐下来 听我说
...but I need to know that you're listening to me, okay?
我 我快要疯了 他要死了 我却不知该做
I'm- I'm in a fucking state. lt's like he's going, and I don't-
好吧 告诉我些实际的 比如处理遗体什么的
Just tell me practical things, like what the fuck do I do with his body?
死的时候我该做什么? 下一步怎么办 然后呢?
What do I do when he dies? What next? What happens then? What next?
援助会将做这些
That's what Hospice can take care of.
他们会派一个护士过去
They'll send over a nurse, somebody who-
不 他已经有菲尔在那儿了
No. Phil. He has Phil now.
菲尔是派过去的护士么?
- Phil is one of the nurses from the service? - Yeah.
如果你对菲尔满意的话 就让他继续做着
lf you're happy with Phil taking care of him and helping you, that's fine...
但是最好联系援助会让他们来处理尸体
...but contact Hospice to arrange for the body.
你不懂得的
You don't understand. lt's-
现在他一天比一天痛苦 那些狗屁药片一点用都没有
There's more pain than before, and the fucking morphine pills aren't working...
这两天 他根本连咽东西都不行
...and it's like- The past two days, he can't really swallow...
我根本不知道药能不能咽下去
...and l, um- I don't know if the pills are going down.
我根本看不见他嘴里 我一晚上只能看着他
I can't see inside his mouth anymore, and I'm up all night staring at him...
我根本不知道药咽下去没有 他在呻吟 他太难受了
...and I don't know if the pills are going down. He moans and he hurts.
我们有办法的 我可以给他
We can fix that, because I can give you-
你在听吗?
Are you listening?
在听 我感觉好些了 要坐下吗?
- Yeah. I'm listening. I'm getting better. - Do you wanna sit down?
我得坐一会儿
I need to sit down.
厄尔恐怕撑不下去了
Okay, Linda, EarI's not gonna make it.
他就快不行 他就要 非常快
He's dying. He is. He's dying very, very rapidly.
我们需要做的就是 尽可能地结束
The thing here is to make this experience...
这种痛苦和折磨 让他轻松一些离去
...as painless and easy for him as possible.
懂了么?
You understand?
救助会能接手这一切过程
Now, Hospice will take care of all the technical things.
他们帮助你处理他的遗体
They will help you. They will take care of the body.
只需要在他离去后打个电话
They are who you call when he dies.
这是救助会的号码
There's the number of Hospice.
还有就是 除了以前开的吗啡药片外
Okay. Now, as far as the morphine pills go...
还有一种药可以考虑一下
...there's something else to consider.
有一种效果非常显著的液体吗啡疗法
There's a very strong, very potent solution of liquid morphine...
一小瓶吗啡 放在眼药滴瓶里
...and it's a little bottle. lt has an eyedropper.
这样能很方便的滴进他的咽喉部
lt's easy to get into his mouth and drop on his tongue...
立刻就能消除他的体内痛苦
...and it will certainly diminish the pain that he's in.
但是你必须知道 一旦使用这种药
But you need to realize that, uh, once you give it to him...
他就不可能痊愈了
...there really is no going back.
这东西肯定会去除痛苦 但会立刻让他失去知觉
lt will certainly cure his pain, but he will drift in and out of consciousness...
这将比现在还要糟
...even worse than he is now, Linda. I mean...
厄尔 将会完全没有知觉 将不是厄尔了
All sign of the recognizable Earl will pretty much go away.
我还能说什么呢? 不知道这样行么
l- What the fuck can I say to- ? I don't know what to say to that.
我不想这样
I don't want to do this.
这么坐着
Sit here.
看得到东西
I can see the things, you know.
我什么都知道 狗日的
lt's getting there, that's the cocksucker.
我看得到那支笔
I see that pen.
我看得见它 就是这个
I see it. I know it's there.
我够到它
I reach for it.
不
No.
有什么用?
No. No goddamn use.
知道吗 我有个儿子
I have a son, you know.
- 是吗? - 是
- You do? - Yeah.
- 他在哪? - 不知道
- Where is he? - I don't know.
我知道
I mean...
就在这里
...he's around, but...
他就在镇上 但我不知道在哪儿
He's here in town, but I don't know.
知道么
You know...
他很倔的
...he's a tough one.
非常倔
Very....
- 菲尔 有女朋友吗你? - 没有
- Got a girlfriend, Phil? - No.
- 赶快找一个 - 我在努力
- Get a girlfriend. - I'm trying.
做些漂亮的事儿 和她一起
Do good things with her. Share the things.
就像那些狗屁话说的
- All that bullshit is true, you know. - Yeah.
找个好的 抓住她不放 然后就成功了
Find a good one, hold on, and all that.
琳达人呢?
Where's Linda?
她有点事儿出去了
She went out. She, uh, said she went out to run some errands.
马上就回来
- She'll be back. - Oh.
她是个好女孩
- She's a good girl. - Yeah.
就是有点傻 不过还算是好女孩
She's a little nuts. Heh. But she's a good girl, I think. Yeah.
她就是有点傻
- She's a little daffy. Yeah. - Yeah.
她爱你
She loves you.
嗯 可能吧
Well, maybe.
- 是 - 对
- Yeah. - Yeah.
她是个挺好的女孩
She is a good one.
你最后一次和儿子说话是什么时候?
When's the last time you talked to your son?
不记得了
I don't know.
十
Ten.
可能是十 或者五
Maybe ten.... Five...
操
Fuck.
又一样东西没掉了
That's another thing that goes.
你的记忆? 时间顺序 懂吗?
- Your memory? - Time lines, you know?
我能记起事情 但是不知道何时发生的
I can remember things, but not right there.
- 明白吗? - 明白
- You know? - Yeah.
明白?明白个屁
Yeah? What the fuck do you know?
以前见到过这样的 像我这样的傻逼?
- I've seen it before. - Oh, other fucking assholes like me?
- 没有人像你一样 - 狗日的
- Ah, there's no asshole like you. - Cocksucker.
为什么每句话都这种词儿 狗日的 混蛋 或者 傻逼?
How come every word you use is either cocksucker, shit balls, or fuck?
- 你知道你该做什么吗? - 去死?
- Do me a personal favor. - Go fuck myself.
真他妈聪明
- You got it. - Ha, ha.
我不能
I can't...
我再也受不了这些了
I can't hold on to this any longer.
再给你来点吗啡好吗? 不 把电话给我
- I'll get another pill. Another morphine pill. - No. Give me the fucking phone.
要打给谁? 我要打给他
- Who you gonna call? - I wanna see this. l, uh-
- 到底在哪儿? - 谁?
- Where is he? Do you know? - Who?
- 杰克 - 你儿子叫杰克?
- Jack. - ls Jack your son?
你想要给他打电话是么?
Do you want to call him on the phone? I can call him.
我帮你打 你记得号码吧
I can dial the number if you can remember the number.
不是他
lt's not him.
不是杰克 他是个傻逼
lt's not him. He's a fucking asshole.
菲尔 快来 难受死了
Oh, Phil, come here. This is so boring.
受不了这些
So goddamn.... Goddamn....
什么遗嘱
You know, that dying wish...
什么一个躺在床上老头
...and all that old man on a bed....
想要最后他妈的
- Wants one thing. - lt's okay.
最后
Find him on a....
弗兰克
Frank.
他叫弗兰克・麦吉
His name is Frank Mackey.
- 弗兰克・麦吉? - 对
- Frank Mackey? - Yeah.
你的儿子?
That's your son?
反正不是我名字
Not my name.
去找找
Go find...
找找莉莉
Find Lily.
把这个给我 给我
Give me that. Give me.
给我 给我的话
Give me- lf you give me that...
就在那儿
...over there on, uh....
操 我做不了
Oh. Fuck. I can't hold on to this.
我懂了
I got it. I got it.
是
Yeah.
啊
Ah.
阴茎万岁!
Respect the cock.
摧毁她们的下体!
And tame the cunt.
摧毁她们!
Tame it.
掌握技巧 勇往直前 我将教会你们 我们必须
Take it on headfirst with the skills that I will teach you at work...
- 懂得说不 - 不
- ...and say, No. - AUDlENCE: No!
你控制不了我! 不!
- You will not control me. No! AUDlENCE: No!
你不可能勾引我! 不!
- You will not take my soul. No! AUDlENCE: No!
你不可能胜利!
You will not win this game.
这仅仅是一场游戏 伙计们
Because it is a game, guys. You wanna think it's not, huh?
想想你的学校生活
You go back to the schoolyard...
当时还迷恋那个大奶玛莉・简
...and you have that crush on big- titted Mary Jane.
阴茎万岁
Respect the cock.
你必须牢牢记着
You are embedding this thought:
我才是主人!
- I am the one who's in charge. Yeah.
只有我才能说 好吧 !
- I am the one who says, Yes. AUDlENCE: Yes!
不!
- No. AUDlENCE: No!
快点!
- Now. AUDlENCE: Now!
过来!
Here.
这世界就该是这样 大家
Because it's universal, man.
不论什么进化论 什么人类学
lt is evolutional. lt is anthropological.
- 什么生物学 - 是
- lt is biological. - Yeah.
我们是动物
lt is animal.
我们
We...
是
...are...
男人!
...men.
你需要问自己你可以做什么
You need to ask yourself what you can do...
- 是格蕾丝么? - 是
- You Gwenovier? - Yeah.
我是玛费 弗兰克的私人助理
I'm Captain Muffy, Frank's assistant.
- 这是唐尼 我们从这边进去 - 抱歉 我来晚了
- This is Doc. We can go in right here. - Sorry I'm late.
他已经开始35分钟了
He started about 35 minutes ago...
不过现在恐怕刚进入高潮
...but he's probably getting all pumped up right now.
请看这一页最上面 写的什么?
Look down at the top of the page. At the top of the page, what does it say?
做一个时间表! 对 做个时间表 这基本不用强调了
AUDlENCE: Get a calendar. Right. I cannot stress this enough.
现在非常流行 大家都在讲时间表
lt's a simple item. lt's 99 cents at the corner store.
但你要仔细往下看 再往下
But if you look into your packs, reach deep into your packs...
你会看到我们这个时间表非常特别
...you will see that I have been nice enough to include one. See?
我们就是这么独树一帜
Yeah, yeah. That's just the kind of prick I am.
你们需要一个这样的时间表 虽然看上去很简单
You're gonna need this calendar. lt doesn't seem like much.
很普通的一个小玩意儿
lt's a simple item. lt is a small item...
但它将重新改变你的生活
...but it is going to make all the difference in your world.
你认识了一个女孩
You meet a girl, work an A- 3 interruption.
你们下一次见面是八天以后
Let's say an eight- day waiting period before next contact.
你怎么才能知道第八天是什么日子?
How are you gonna know when those eight days are up?
标记的日历
AUDlENCE: Mark the calendar.
没错 你的在日历上做标记
That's right. Mark the calendar. You're gonna mark that calendar.
标在时间表上 要听我的 按照时间表
You're going to stick with me and this calendar.
你必须为自己定一个目标
You're gonna set goals.
这样才能让你们的关系更进一步
lf you really, really wanna make that friend something else...
为此你一定要努力
...you're gonna have to be tough on yourself.
必须设定一个目标
You're gonna have to set goals.
你 呃 穿棕色短袖衫的那位先生
Uh, you, sir, in the, uh, brown short- sleeve shirt.
我看不到你的牌子 你叫什么?
I can't read your name tag. What's your name, please?
- 你好 - 弗兰克在吗?
- Hello. - Hi, uh, is Frank there?
错了 你号码不对
- No, you have the wrong number. - Um...
不好意思 我想找一个叫弗兰克・麦吉的
I'm sorry. I'm looking for a Frank Mackey.
没有叫弗兰克的
Yeah, no, there's no Frank here.
这里是 818- 775- 3993 么?
ls this, um, 818- 775- 3993?
对 那恐怕是你号码记错了
Yeah. No, you have the wrong number.
对了 那么有没有一个叫杰克的呢?
Do you know a Jack, by any chance?
只是一个简单的采访
Just a regular deal. Loosers and tighters.
- 我们会在楼上准备好的 - 谢了
- We're all set upstairs. And then she called me up...
她打电话给我 问我对他的意见
...and she asked me for advice about a guy.
- 准备好了么? - 都好了
- Got everything you need? - All set, thanks.
她知道你对此有什么感受吗?
Does she know how you feel about her? Have you discussed that?
是的 有的
Yes. Absolutely.
怎么说的?
And what does she say?
她说她对我一点感觉都没有
She says she doesn't feel that way about me.
我肯定这屋子里所有人 都能理解你的感受 杰夫
I don't think there's anyone in this room that doesn't understand that pain...
谢谢你和大家分享这一切
...and I wanna thank you for sharing that with us.
我们要教教德尼丝 我们先做好这个时间表 设好目标
Let me tell you what we're gonna teach Denise when we set goals, all right?
我想着 德尼丝
What I say is, Denise.
德尼丝这个小东西
Denise the Piece.
好吧 那就把它记下来 写在时间表上
I mark it down. Oh, I write it up.
你已经被我盯上了
And you have been warned...
我用我的激光
...because I have my lasers...
我的泰瑟枪 我的制导炸弹
... I have my Tasers, I have my lCBMs...
我用我的火箭筒 我的战斗机都对准了你
... I have my bazookas, I have my jets pointed right at you.
好吧 我亲爱的兄弟们 该是我们庆祝的时候了
Because me and my brothers, we like to celebrate...
一进入五月 就是让她爽得合不拢腿的胜利日
...and on the first of May, we celebrate V- Day.
六月时 是我们的吮指鸡块日
And come June, oh, baby, it is the lick of my spoon.
到了八月 好吧 我们要庆祝
Come August, we like to celebrate...
美味腊肠狂欢节!
...Saint Suck My Big Fat Fucking Sausage.
上掉她仅仅是我为自己定的一个目标而已
I set goals for myself...
目标达到后 我对自己说 已经结束了
...and when I say I do not wanna take it anymore...
那么我就会结束这段关系
... I will not take it anymore.
杰夫 你认为她真的是你的朋友吗?
You think she's your friend, Geoff? You think she's your friend?
这些女人根本不能成为朋友
They're not your friends.
难道你真的以为她们能与你共度难关 相濡以沫吗?
Do you really think she's gonna be there when things go bad?
她们真能在你人生不顺利的时候 陪伴着你 支持着你吗?
Huh, guys? When things go wrong, do you think they're gonna be there for us?
根本不可能
Ho- ho, you think again.
上了 这个小娘们
Oh, fucking Denise, Denise the Piece...
我要吃你的小面包圈 你逃不掉的
...you are gonna give me that cherry pie, sweet mama baby.
好 但要注意一点: 并不是说 我们完全不需要女性朋友
Oh, yeah, but listen up. That is not to say that we don't all need females as friends.
请注意 我们马上在第二十三章会学到 结交一些可爱女生做朋友
We're gonna learn later that having a couple of chick friends lying around...
将会对我们设置嫉妒陷阱极其便捷 稍后就会学到这个
...comes in real handy in setting jealousy traps. We'll get to that later.
现在 请大家拿出蓝色小册子 第18页
Right now, what I want you guys to do is pull out your blue booklets, page 18.
我们加快速度浏览一遍 稍后再详细讲解
We're going quickly. We're gonna workshop it later.
第18页 蓝色小册子
Eighteen, blue booklet.
制造一次不幸
Form A Tragedy.
非常简单 非常明了 但如果制造成功的话
This is simple and clean, and if done correctly...
能够事半功倍
...can be very, very effective in getting some bush.
举个例子 给你这位目标小姐打个电话 安排个约会
Here we go. You call up your so- called friend and set a date.
比如定在7:30左右 打电话这么说
Let's say make it around 7:30. You call her on the phone.
喂?
Hello?
你好 克劳迪娅在吗?
Hi. Uh, is Claudia here?
她还在睡
She's sleeping.
你是她男朋友?
Are you- ? Are you her boyfriend?
你 你是吉米・加托吧?
You're Jimmy Gator, right?
嗯 你叫什么名字?
That's right. What's your name?
我叫雷
I'm Ray.
- 哦 你是她男朋友么? - 不是 只是普通朋友
- So are you her boyfriend? - No, I'm just a friend.
明白
I see.
- 来这儿做什么啊? - 我是她父亲
- Ha, ha, what are you doing here? I mean- - I'm her father.
能进去吗?
Mind if I come in?
当然 谢谢
- Yeah, sure. - Thanks.
怎么回事? 是我 克劳迪娅 我
CLAUDlA: What the fuck is this? JlMMY: lt's me, Claudia. lt's me.
你来干什么? 你跑来干什么?
What do you want? Why are you here?
我有话想和你说 你男朋友让我进来的
I'd like to talk to you. Uh, your boyfriend let me in. I just-
他不是我男朋友
That's not my boyfriend.
- 想骂我淫贱是吧? - 不 不是的
- Wanna call me a slut now or something? - No, I don't.
你他妈到底来做什么?
What the fuck do you want?
我只是想坐下来 我有话想对你说 不许坐下!
- I wanna sit. I wanna talk to you. - Don't sit down.
我只是想 噢 太多事情要说了
I want to, uh- God, I want so many things.
我想或许我们应该好好谈谈
- Maybe we could talk- - I don't wanna talk to you.
我不想和你说话! 我有很多事想对你说 我不想和你说话!
- There's things I have to talk to you about. - I don't want to talk to you.
没事 没事 不一定现在说
That's all right. lt doesn't have to be now.
我们可以约个时间 随便什么时候
We can make a date to set some other time.
我真的不是故意闯进来的
I didn't mean to walk in on you like this.
你为什么要来? 为什么这么做?
Why are you here? Why are you doing this? Coming in here?
想说我像妓女是吧?
- You wanna call me a whore? - No, l- Claudia....
我真的不想被你想成这样
I don't want you to think I'm that way to you.
- 我怎么会骂你淫贱呢 - 呵呵 是么?
- I'm not gonna call you a slut or something. - Yeah, ha, ha. Yeah, right.
那么到底来干什么?
What are you doing here?
你他妈到我房子到底来干什么!
What the fuck are you doing in my house?
别喊好吗 宝贝儿 别这么生气
Please don't yell, honey. Just don't go crazy.
我没有生气! 别老说我在生气!
I'm not crazy! Don't you tell me that I'm crazy!
我病了 克劳迪娅
Claudia, I'm sick. I'm sick, Claudia.
放屁! 不是的 听我说
- Fuck you. - No, no, please, listen to me.
- 我靠 - 听我说 克劳迪娅
- Fuck you! - Listen to me right now, Claudia.
我快死了
I am dying.
我病的很重 快不行了
I got sick, and then I felI down-
放屁! 滚出去 别在我屋子呆着!
Fuck you! Get the fuck out of my house.
我快死了 我得了癌症 克劳迪娅
I'm dying. I have cancer, Claudia.
我得了癌症
I have cancer.
我马上就死了
- And I'm dying very soon. - Fuck you.
- 已经蔓延到骨骼了 - 放屁!
- lt's metastasized in my bones. - Fuck you!
我不骗你 我说的是真的
Claudia, it's.... I'm not lying to you. This is the truth.
克劳迪娅 我真的 我真的要完蛋了
I'm telling you, Claudia, I'm going to lose.
出去
Get out.
快滚出去!
Get out! Get the fuck out of here!
出去! 滚! 你妈妈很想你
- Get out! Go! - Your mother would like to hear from you.
放屁 滚!
Fuck you. Get out!
快点滚出去!
Get the fuck out of my house now!
滚!
Get out!
保持你的身体运行良好
Keep your body running good.
预防最重要
Prevention is everything.
如果你不去维护 我将会修理
lf you don't maintain it, I'll be fixing it.
强身健体 保持身体健康
Keep fit. Stay healthy.
如果你的车运行良好 带他去杰菲润滑油店
If your car is running good, take it to Jiffy Lube...
他们会提供彭泽尔润滑油
...and they offer Pennzoil.
预防
Prevention.
这是它的价值
lt's worth it.
嘿 你不想看到我的
Hey, you don't wanna see me.
唐尼
AVl: Don.
嘿 阿维
Hey, Avi.
马上过去
Just one sec.
跟贴满向下看的发胶说再见吧
Say goodbye to the plastered- down look of heavy hairspray...
跟自然看打个招呼
...and hello to the natural- looking-
- 求你了 - 别这样
- Please. Don't, Donnie. Don't do this.
别这样乱来 所罗门 我什么都没做!
This is so fucked, Solomon! I don't deserve this!
别装得这么激动 丹尼尔 再清楚不过了
Don't get strong, Donnie. This is making sense.
再明白不过了
This is making a lot of sense.
你没做好我给你的工作
You are not doing the job. The job I ask you to do.
我送给你的工作
A job I give you.
一而再 再而三地!
Over and over and over.
我很抱歉 不过以后再也不会这样了 真的
I'm sorry, but I'm not gonna say I'm sorry much more.
我现在身无分文了 所罗门 你要是现在辞掉我
I don't have any money, Solomon. lf you fire me-
我会付钱给你的! 把薪水付给你!
I pay you. I give you a paycheck.
吃白食的东西 唐尼
Your sales suck, Don.
给你钱! 给你!
I give. I give.
我发现你时 我看见你时 记得么
When I find you, when I meet you, what?
我把你的名字写在他妈的广告牌上
I put your name up on a fucking billboard.
我让你进我的店 做我的销售
I put you in my store. My salesman.
他妈的做我的索罗门电子代言人!
My fucking representation of Solomon Solomon Electronic.
挑战赛里的神童 丹尼尔・史密斯
The Quiz Kid, Donnie Smith, from the game show.
是啊 我把名气给你了 我的名字!没错!
I lent you my celebrity, my name. Exactly.
放屁! 放屁! 我给够你钱了! 给够了!
Oh, fuck you. Fuck you. I paid you! I paid you!
我他妈给你多少机会 一次又一次 我受够了!
I gave you a fucking chance, and a chance, over and over, and you let me down!
我怎么会这么相信你!
I trust you with so much!
给你我店里钥匙 我锁的密码 我生意的一切!
Keys to my store. The codes to my locks. The life and blood of my business.
你呢 你全花在这里!
ln return, you smash in 7- Eleven!
每次都迟到! 我还借你钱!
And late! Always late! Loans!
借给你被你骗去做你的什么厨房!
The loans for your kitchen that you never did.
我还了!
I paid you back!
我是从你薪水里扣两年扣回来的!
Two years! Two years later, and from your paycheck!
连利息都没要!
I never charged interest.
所罗门 求求你 求你了!
Solomon, please. Please.
你这样我就完蛋了!
I am so fucked here if you do this.
我从没想过会被辞掉 我会完蛋的!
This is the worst timing. The worst timing I could ever imagine.
我必须得工作!
I need to keep working.
我还有一堆债务 还有一堆
I have so many debts, so many things.
还要付我的手术钱!
I have- I have- I have- I have my surgery.
- 我马上要做口腔手术了 - 什么手术?
- My oral surgery coming. - What surgery?
口腔手术! 牙齿矫正手术!
Oral surgery. Corrective teeth surgery.
- 那是干啥的? - 牙箍!
What is that? - Braces.
- 你要什么牙箍 - 我需要的!
You don't need braces. - Yes, I do.
- 你牙齿一点问题都没有 - 我需要手术!
AVl: Your teeth are straight. - I need surgery!
牙齿矫正手术!
I need corrective oral surgery.
你在度假时被闪电劈傻了是吧?
Donnie, you got struck by lightning that time in Tahoe.
你绝对不需要什么牙箍
I don't think braces is a good idea.
所罗门 再给我一次机会吧 求你了
Solomon, just let me ask you once, please.
别这样对我
Please don't do this.
- 你拿什么付你那牙箍钱? - 我不知道!
AVl: How are you paying for the braces? - I don't know.
装个牙箍要多少钱?
Well, that's just incredible. How much are braces, anyway?
这是 这是两码事
lt's, uh... lt doesn't matter.
好像要5000块 我看到过
AVl: lt's, like, $5000. I've seen it. I know. - Now you're pissing me off.
你他妈的要气死我了 你疯了吗!?
This is incredible. This is fucking stupid.
你要花5000块装什么狗屁牙箍?!
You're paying $5000 for braces you don't need?
- 我以前也非常出色的 - 别
- I've been a good worker. - Don't.
- 别提这些 丹尼尔 - 你从哪儿拿钱做手术?
- No need for braces. - Where are you gonna get the money?
- 我不知道! - 你想找我要!我就知道
- I don't know. - You were going to ask me.
- 我以前那么出色 我 - 根本不需要牙箍
- I have been a good worker. - No need for braces, Donnie.
你别瞎掺合!
That is none of your business!
我以前多么卖命多么死心塌地地为你干活 你这个混蛋!
I've been a good and loyal worker for you, you fucking assholes!
- 嘿 你给我小心点 - 把钥匙给我
- Hey, fuck you. Watch it, now. - Give me your keys.
把他妈钥匙还给我!
- No, don't- - Give me your fucking keys!
推定他叫波特・帕克 59岁
OFFlCER 1: ldentified as Porter Parker, age 59...
他就是壁橱里这个死人
...better known as the dead guy in the closet.
管理员说这是她丈夫
Says the building guy, this is her husband.
他不住这里
DETECTlVE 1: He comes around, raises some shit...
他来找她 后来就听见他们吵架 打斗声和尖叫
...screaming and yelling something.
还有儿子和一个小孩
There's a son and a kid.
- 她的儿子? - 对 还有一个小孩
- Her son? - Her son. That's right. And the kid.
他们也在这儿 从昨晚开始
They were here, and from late last night...
一直到今早 一直有尖叫和吵嚷声
...and through the morning, screaming and yelling.
- 他们现在在哪? - 还没找到
- Where are they? DETECTlVE 1: They are not to be found.
床边找到600块钱和一大盒保险套
She's got $600 and a large box of condoms next to the bed.
- 这女人太凶了 - 三个结婚戒指
- She was real belligerent- OFFlCER 2: Three wedding rings.
一整天都有人进进出出 管理员这么说的
Guys coming in and out all day. This is the building guy talking.
管理员还说她儿子和壁橱里这位经常打
OFFlCER 1: Building guy says the son and the closet guy are always going at it.
- 她怎么说? - 什么都没说
DETECTlVE 2: And what is she saying? OFFlCER 1: Not a goddamn thing.
谢了 兰迪
Thanks, Randy. Whoa!
我帮了你 你得付多少钱?
How much you pay me for my help?
事情没那么简单 小伙计
lt's more complicated than that, little man.
先给我钱我来帮你破案吧
Put me on the payroll and find out. Find out what's up.
你又没申请做警察
Okay, you don't just sign up to be a police officer.
必须先经过三年的训练 我已经训练好了 我没问题的
- lt's about three years of training, okay? - I'm trained. I'm ready to go.
- 不然买点糖果吧? - 不要 小家伙 不好意思
- You wanna buy some candy to help- ? - No. No, sorry, little man.
你想听我的陈述吗? 我可以表演给你看
You wanna take my statement? I'll perform for you.
不过是要钱的
- Gotta get paid, though. Gotta get paid. - Mm- hm.
你今天为什么没去上学?
Why aren't you in school today?
今天不用上 老师病了
No school today. My teacher got sick.
你们没有代课老师吗?
Oh, you don't have substitute teachers where you go to school?
没有 他们在里面发现什么了啊?
No. So, what did they find out in there?
这是机密 小家伙
JlM: That is confidential information, little man.
告诉我吧 我就告诉你
DlXON: Tell me what you know. I'll tell you what I know.
不可能
JlM: No can do.
把案子留给那些侦探 他们屁都查不出来
DlXON: Leave this one to the detectives, they ain't gonna solve shit.
我能帮你的 让你成为大红人
I can help you. Make you the man with the plan.
我可以把真相告诉你
Give you the gift that I flow. Think fast.
- 你想知道谁杀了他吗? - 过来 你
- You wanna know who killed that guy? - Okay. You come here.
- 不 - 过来
- DlXON: No. - Come here.
过来 你是想轻视法律捍卫者吗?
You wanna disrespect an officer of the law?
我能帮你解决这个案子的 告诉你是谁做的
I can help you solve the case. I can tell you who did it.
你是笑星是吧? 要给我说笑话是吧?
Oh, you're a joker, huh? Telling me jokes?
- 我是饶舌歌手 - 哦 你是个饶舌歌手 好的
- I'm a rapper. - Oh, you're a rapper. Oh, okay.
- 出唱片了吗? - 还没呢
- You got a record contract? - Not yet.
你要相信我的 我会告诉你的
Give you a clue for the bust if you show me some trust.
你以前又去过少年大厅?
You ever been to juvenile hall?
我他妈才不和你一样呢!
I ain't fucking with you!
小心你说的话 小心点
Hey, watch the mouth. Watch it.
来吧 哥们 看着我
Come on, man, just watch me.
看着我 听我说
Watch and listen.
好
Okay.
存在 随着双屁股意义的礼物 我赐给
Presence. With the double- ass- meaning gifts I bestow
我的即兴反复片段和我的身体流动 虽然你不听我
With my riff and my flow But you don't hear me, though
想快点 来追我吧你
Think fast, catch me, yo
因为我把我所知道的有了共鸣
'Cause I throw what I know With a resonance
你这个麻烦的臭家伙 乳臭未干
For your trouble- ass fiend in weaning yourself
从货架的后面出来
Off of the back of the shelf
贾卡斯饼干 身体堆垛机
Jackass crackers, body- stackers
迪克短鸣 黑鬼 自慰触发器
Dick- tooting niggers Masturbating your triggers
停 停 不要用这些词儿
Hold it, homeboy. I don't need to hear that word.
生活随着你的肩膀上的芯片变老
Living to get older With a chip on your shoulder
除非你认为你有把握 因为你的臀部得到了一个皮套
Except you think you got a grip 'Cause your hip got a holster
是不是没有忏悔 因此 克星 你最好他妈的闭嘴
Ain't no confessor, so, buster, you better just shut the fuck up
尝试聆听和学习
Try to listen and learn
可以了 酷哥 我可不愿意再听你的脏字儿了
Whoa, cut it, Coolio. I've had enough of the mouth and the language.
马上就完了!
I'm almost done.
那赶快说完
Finish it up without the lip.
检查自我 摘下来 我是先知
Check that ego Come off it, I'm the prophet
这位教授 我要去教你的蠕虫
The professor I'm gonna teach you about the Worm
最终转向追赶沉船 随着长时间的压迫颈部
Who eventually turned to catch wreck With the neck of a long- time oppressor
他正在从魔鬼那里奔逃 但债务总是增加
And he's running from the devil But the debt is always gaining
而如果他的身价被伤害 他的价值带来的疼痛
And if he's worth being hurt He's worth bringing pain in
当阳光不工作 上帝会带来雨
When the sunshine don't work The good Lord bring the rain in
好了 这些会帮助你破掉这案子的
Now, that shit will help you solve the case.
不管是啥意思
Okay. Whatever that meant.
我肯定这会有用的 酷男
I'm sure it's real helpful, lce- T.
你有听我说吗?
DlXON: Did you listen to me?
有啊 有听
I was listening to you.
我在告诉你谁干的 你竟然听都不听
I told you who did it, and you're not even listening to me.
我一直都很配合你
I'm through playing games.
继续努力 乖乖地呆在学校
Be cool. Stay in school, okay?
别在这里站着了
Get out of the street now.
快走
Move it.
- 快 咱们快走 - 是你晚了 不是我
RlCK: Come on, let's go. - You're late, not me.
- 你本应该在前面的 - 我刚没看到你
RlCK: You could have been in front. - I didn't see you from the window.
你为什么不
Well, you- Why didn't you just, uh- ? I don't know.
为什么不坐在前排? 快
You could have come in the front. I don't know. Hurry up.
听着 准备好再次获胜了吗? 当然
- All right, you ready to keep winning? - Sure.
没事吧?
RlCK: You okay?
我膝盖差点撞坏了刚才
Busted my ankle there.
等等让化妆师把你头发整整
You gotta have that makeup lady fix your hair.
全是水
Okay. - Okay? lt's really wet.
- 你终于到了 - 不好意思我们迟了
- There you are. There you are. - I'm sorry we're late, Cynthia.
- 没关系的 - 刚才塞车了
- Oh, that's all right. - RlCK: We got caught in traffic.
- 你的书没事 你怎么样? - 我没事
- Your book is okay. How you doing? - I'm fine.
是吗?准备好了吗?
Yeah? Yeah, you ready to go, go, go?
知道有谁参与艾伦・塞克的事情吗?
Know anybody involved in that Alan Thicke thing?
科里・哈伊姆的事情吗? 在高中的恐怖分子?
The Corey Haim thing? Terrorist in the high school?
- 呃 不 - 理查德和茱莉亚呢?
- Uh, no. - Where's Richard and Julia?
都到了 都好着呢
Oh, good. Um, they're here. They're fine.
他们正在更衣室 好了 我们都准备好了
They're in the dressing room, so we're all set.
- 待会见 - 加油 好孩子
- Okay. See you later. - You go to it, handsome.
- 再见 - 好的 爱你
- See you. - Okay, buddy, love you.
- 祝你好运 里克 - 嘿 皮特
- Good luck, Rick. - Hey, Peter.
迪克 对不起 迪克
Dick, Dick. I'm sorry. Dick.
操 老记不住这破名字
Fuck. Can't get that fucking name.
今晚他们要破纪录了对吧? 差不多了
- Who's ready to beat the record? JULlA'S DAD: That was close.
那些人都是小菜一碟
RlCK: lt's cats and fucking dogs out there. - Cats and dogs indeed.
绝对是小菜一碟 去年后我就没见过这么大的雨
RlCK: I've never seen it rain this bad since last year...
是因拉尔尼诺还是厄尔尼诺什么的吧 不管叫什么
...because of La Nina or El Nino or whatever the shit.
是厄尔尼诺 不好意思我来晚了
RlCK: Sorry I'm late.
- 再问一次你叫什么来着? - 艾米・珍妮丝小姐
- What was your name again? - Amy, Mr. Jennings.
叫我 D・J 听着
DlCK: Call me D.J. You said Amy, right? Listen.
相信我 保持注意
Trust me, you know. But stay focused.
新闻部在演播室什么地方?
Where's the news department?
- 在楼上 - 你有去过吗?
CYNTH lA: lt's upstairs. - Have you ever been there?
当然 怎么啦?
Oh, sure. Why?
我想知道气象部门的情况
I was wondering about the weather department.
- 嗯 - 我不知道是否有天气预报员
- Uh- huh. - I was wonder whether the weather people...
通过外面的气象服务
...have outside meteorological services...
还是自己用仪器来做
...or if they have in- house instruments.
我可以帮你查一查 等会儿我们可以参观一下
Um, I can check on that, and later we can take a tour.
- 哦 好 - 声音怎么样?
- Oh, okay. - Sounds good?
问这个是因为外面在下雨吗?
- You asking because it's raining outside? - I guess.
应该是吧 坚持观察发生的任何事 是吧?
Uh- huh. What do you do? Whatever's happening, you look into?
- 就像那样? - 我不知道
- Something like that? - I don't know.
不知道吗?这是个好习惯
Ha, ha, you don't know, huh? Well, it's not a bad way to be.
对身边任何事保持兴趣
lnterested in everything that's going around.
湿 潮湿 应该很简单的东西吧
Wet- Wet is wet. Just that simple.
- 嗨 玛莉 - 嗨 斯坦利
- Hi, Mary. - Hi, hon, Stanley.
生产
Production.
露丝在线上 这些是今天要用的卡片
Rose is on the phone. Here are the cards for today.
- 我还得15分钟熟悉一下卡片 - 不好意思
- Fifteen minutes to go over those cards. - Sorry.
- 帮我找一下葆拉 - 你想现在找她?
- Find Paula for me. - You want her right now?
- 对 现在 - 再二十分钟就开播了
- Yes, now. - We're on the air in 20 minutes.
快去 玛莉 喂? 嗨
Fucking hell, Mary. Yeah, hi.
- 嗨 你怎么样? - 我在喝酒
- Hi, how you doing? I'm drinking.
- 快还是慢? - 再快不过了
- Slowly or quickly? - As fast as I can.
做完节目回家吧
You come home soon after the show.
我去见她了
I went to see her.
一个混蛋穿着内衣的混蛋开的门
Some fucking asshole answers the door in his underwear.
可能都有五十岁了
He's 50 years old.
桌上全是可乐什么的
There's coke and shit laid out on the table.
她和你说话了么?
Did she talk to you?
她简直疯了 她疯了 露丝
She went crazy. She went fucking crazy, Rose.
- 你告诉她了吗? - 我不知道算不算
- Did you tell her? - Oh, I don't know.
得挂了 没时间了
I gotta go. I don't have time.
还得再喝些酒
I got a lot more drinking to do before I go on.
- 我爱你 - 我也爱你
- I love you. - Love you too.
妈的
Shit.
- 喂? - 警察! 快开门!
- Hello? - JlM: Police! Open the door!
谁?
Who is it?
警察! 开门!
JlM: lt's the LAPD! Open the door!
来了!
CLAUDlA: I'm coming!
我得先穿上衣服!
I have to get dressed!
快一点儿好吗! 把门打开!
You're not coming fast enough! Open the door!
你没听见吗? 我说马上了 马上就好!
Didn't you hear me? I said I'm coming, and that means I'm coming!
我得先衣服 好吗?
I just have to get dressed, all right?
我要先把衣服穿好!
I really- I have to get dressed!
我讨厌什么都说不清楚就来这里
I hate coming here and not being able to talk.
我知道 没关系
lt's fine. I understand.
希望情况能好些
I wish the circumstance was better.
我不知道会发生什么
I don't know what's gonna happen. lt's so fucked.
我已经坚持不住了 用尽了所有疗法
- I feel so over the top with everything. - Running out of your medication at all...
不管任何时候使用这个都是十分恐怖的
...let alone at a time like this, could be drastic.
谢谢你 丹尼医生
Thank you, Dr. Diane.
即使你的口袋 或者是渔夫的口袋
- even your pocket. And the pocket fisherman's-
这个周六的晚上 7:30
- 7:30 this Saturday night.
1美元99美分 握住它 罗恩 只有四个简单的
- dollars and 99 cents. Hold it, Ron. It's only four easy-
纳斯达克交易价格
NASDAQ trading at-
和他聪明的伙伴
- Stanley Spector and his brilliant friends, Richard and Julia...
理查德和茱莉亚要战胜今天的成年挑战者们 米姆・路易斯和陶德
...can defeat today's adult challengers, Mim, Luis, and Todd.
他们将获得50万美元的团队奖
They're moving towards a half- a- million- dollar team total...
小孩都知道节目的新纪录!
...and a What Do Kids Know? record.
- 粉点外送 - 嗨 我想叫点送货服务
- Pink Dot. - Hi. I'd like to get an order for delivery.
- 电话号码? - 号码是818- 725- 4424
- Phone number? - 818- 725- 4424.
- 帕特里奇? - 对
- Partridge? - Yeah.
想要点什么呢?
What would you like?
我想要花生酱
I'd like to get an order of, um, peanut butter...
香烟 骆驼的 还要水
- Mm- hm. - ...uh, cigarettes, Camel Lights.
- 嗯嗯 - 呃 水
- Mm- hm. - Uh, water...
- 瓶装水么? - 不不 不要水了
- Bottled water? - Um, no. You know what, forget the water.
再来一条面包就好 白面包
- Just give me a loaf of bread. White bread. - Okay.
- 你们有《花花公子》杂志么? - 有
- And, um, do you have Playboy magazine? - Yeah.
- 来一本吧 - 有《阁楼》杂志么?
- Okay. One of those. - And, uh, Penthouse, the magazine?
有是么? 来一本
- Yeah. - You have that? Okay. Uh, one of those.
- 《皮条客》呢? - 有
- And, um, Hustler? - Yeah.
有么?
- Do you have that? - Yeah, I said.
- 有啊 要吗? - 要
- That it? - Yeah, that's it.
还要花生酱 面包和香烟是么?
You still want the peanut butter, bread, and cigarettes?
是啊 怎么了?
Yeah. What?
- 总共31 90 三十分钟内送到 - 谢谢你
- The total is 31.90. Thirty minutes or less. - Okay. Thank you.
- 现金还是信用卡? - 现金
- ls that cash or credit card? - Cash.
- 谢谢你 - 谢谢
- Thanks. - Thank you.
- 再见 - 再见
- Bye. - Bye.
向阴茎敬礼 向小穴进军!
Respect the cock and tame the cunt!
好好享受你们的午餐吧!
Have a great lunch!
这位是格蕾丝 《传记》节目组的 她想给你做个专访
This is Gwenovier from Profiles. She's here for the interview.
- 很高兴见到你 - 久仰 久仰
- Nice to meet you. - I admire your work.
- 谢谢 我们在楼上已经准备好 - 对你来说 这儿很危险的
- Thank you. I have us set up in a suite- - lt's not very safe for you here.
我又完成一个研讨会 格蕾丝
I finish one of these seminars, Gwenovier....
太他妈棒了 我就是蝙蝠侠
I swear to fucking God. I mean, I am Batman.
我就是超人
I'm Superman. I'm like a.... A fucking....
我感觉自己就他妈是动作巨星
I'm like a fucking action hero after that.
我要是现在走出去的话 格蕾丝
I could walk out if this room right now.
下楼到到大厅 然后走到街上
I could go down the hall, walk down the street...
我能把所有小甜妞们带回来 不费吹灰之力
...and pick up any little honey I meet that has even one second to stop.
- 只要一秒钟? - 别打断我 美女
- GWENOVlER: All it takes is one second? - Just one second, girl.
一个眼神 一个沉思
One glance, one hesitation...
我们只需要用眼神交会
...one subtle look my way for me to know...
然后就像这样
...and then it is:
砰! 乓! 咚!
Bing, bang, boom.
噢 不好意思!
Oh, my God. Oh!
我离题太远了
I'm away on a tangent.
- 说真的 - 别激动了 好吗?
- I tell you... - GWENOVlER: Don't hurt yourself, okay?
说真的 太激动了
I tell you, I do.
我一上这种研讨会就太吗的亢奋
I get so fucking jazzed at these seminars...
因为我完全融入其中了
...see, because I am what I believe.
我身体力行
I do as I say.
我自己非常信这些东西
I live by these rules...
我虔诚地遵守它们
...as religiously as I preach them.
所以我才会变得这么疯狂 上窜下跳 左突右冲
That's why I am getting the nasty left, right, center, up, down, sideways.
性爱圣战就要爆发 由麦吉领导的队伍将大获全胜
The Battle of the Bush is being fought and won by Team Mackey.
- 好吧 我们开始录影吧 - 什么? 我以为我们已经在录了
- We're gonna start rolling now. - What? I thought we were rolling.
那快开始吧 快 快 快点 我会毫无保留地对你的
Come on, go, go, go, Gwenovier. I am firing pearls at you here.
我会告诉你 这场战斗其实并不顺利
I want you to know that I'm not succeeding in the bush...
谁让我是弗兰克・T・J・麦吉呢
...because I'm Frank T.J. Mackey. Ah, you think about this.
我是说 有些女人
I mean, there are women...
想要挑战我
...who, uh, wanna destroy me.
是么? 真不敢相信
No. I find that hard to believe.
这使得情势变得严峻 极其严峻
lt makes it very difficult, twice as hard for me.
我在各地巡回时 有些小辣妹
There's some hottie I'm moving in on...
听说了我 我的计划 和我的这些方案
...knows me, knows my, you know, my, uh, plans and my schemes, you know?
她们就想玩我
She's gonna wanna fuck with me.
然后回去和朋友说
She's gonna go back, you know tell her friends: Yada, yada, yada...
弗兰克・T・J・麦吉不过如此嘛
You know, Frank T.J. Mackey, he ain't all that. You know.
其实不过如此 被我玩儿了吧
He ain't all that. Didn't get me.
这让我 让我
So, me, I am...
我必须异常警觉
You know, I'm just on full afterburners...
- 必须在惊涛骇浪中穿梭 - 好吧
- ...full- throttle through hottie heaven. - Okay.
- 左闪 右躲 - 我懂了
- Just dodging left. Dodging right. - Yes, I understand.
- 躲开这些恐怖分子的子弹 - 我不知道这些发生过
- Dodging these bullets from these terrorists. - I should've known this was gonna happen.
别激动啦 坐好 乖乖的
Calm down, take it easy, and be a good boy...
好么 麦吉先生?
...okay, Mr. Mackey?
这才对 坐好
Thank you. Now, you sit back there...
把你的麦克风打开 好吗
...put your microphone on for me, please...
- 好的 女士 - 这样我们才能开始 好吗?
- Yes, ma'am. - So we can do this thing, all right?
没问题
Okay, um....
- 首先我想问你 - 再等一下
- Okay. Let me start by asking you- - Just a second. One second.
还有一个扣子
You missed a button.
谢谢
Thank you.
想知道些什么?
What do you wanna know?
来吧
Make it happen.
我是丹尼尔
This is you, Donnie. Go, go, go.
你好 你又来啦?
Hello. You're back again, huh?
是啊 你好?
Yeah. Yes. Hi.
- 要点什么? - 健怡可乐
- What can I get you? - Uh, Diet Coke.
很累啊 要来一杯吗?
You look tired. You want one of these?
喝你自己的吧
Better pour you one of these, huh?
给我打电话好吗?
WAlTRESS: Can you ring me up?
- 布拉德 看见你真高兴 - 我也是
- Brad, good to see you. - lt's good to see you.
你收到海伦的定金了么?
You make that down payment on the Harley yet?
还没呢 下周再说
Not yet. Not yet. I'll make it next week.
一周六天 你是第一个
Six days. You'll be the first.
我好高兴
Ha, ha, I would love that.
- 再来一杯吧? - 好啊 来吧
- Want another one? - Yes.
我要一杯龙舌兰
Uh, I'd like a tequila.
- 加什么? - 随便
- WAlTRESS: What kind? - lt doesn't matter.
快把门打开!
JlM:Open up the door now!
来了!嘿!
CLAUDlA: Yes, hi! Hello!
耶
Yeah.
不好意思 刚才在穿衣服
I'm sorry. I had to get dressed.
你住这里么?
- You the resident here? - Yes.
一个人?
- You alone in there? - Yes.
里面没有其他人了吗?
No one else in there with you?
没有 怎么啦?
No. What's wrong?
先把你的音乐调小声点好吗?不然什么都听不见
First of all, you're gonna have to turn down the music so we can have a conversation.
能进来吗?
You mind if I come in?
能 进来吧
No. Go ahead.
你的邻居们都非常担心你
You got your neighbors real worried for you.
对不起
I'm sorry.
- 一个人住? - 对
- You live alone? - Yes.
- 你叫什么? - 克劳迪娅
- What's your name? - Claudia.
- 克劳迪娅什么? - 威尔逊
- Claudia what? - Wilson.
好的 克劳迪娅・威尔逊
Okay, Claudia Wilson...
- 你想变聋是么? - 什么?哈哈
- ...are you trying to go deaf? - What? Ha, ha.
- 听清楚我说什么了么? - 是的 不过我不明白
- Did you hear what I just said? - Yes, but I don't know what....
你听音乐时太大声了
Okay. You're listening to your music so loud...
- 这样会使你听力受损的 - 好吧
- ...you're gonna damage your ears. - Okay.
如果你老是把音量调得这么大
lf you continue to listen to your music at that level...
那就不仅仅让你自己听力受损 你邻居们也得受损伤
...you're gonna damage not only your ears, but your neighbors' ears as well.
我刚真没觉察有那么大声
- I didn't realize it was that loud. - Yeah.
看吧 这是听力受损的先兆
Well, that right there is the first sign of hearing loss, okay?
好
Okay.
嗯 电视也在这儿放着
I see you got your TV on there too.
你经常这么音响电视一起开么?
You usually keep that on at the same time?
不知道 怎么了?
I don't know. I mean, um.... What is this?
今天是不是嗑药了啊 克劳迪娅?
- You been doing some drugs today, Claudia? - No.
- 喝酒了是么? - 不 哈哈
- Have you been doing some drinking? - No, ha, ha.
好
Okay.
我接到了扰民投诉
I got a call of a disturbance here.
音乐声音太大 还有尖叫和吵闹声
Some loud music, A, and some screaming and yelling.
是不是之前有尖叫和吵闹呢?
Has there been some screaming and yelling here?
是的
Yes.
刚才有人跑到我这里
I had someone come to my door.
我不愿意看见的人
Someone that I didn't want here.
然后我叫他走 就是这样
And I told them to leave, so it's no big deal.
然后就走了 实在抱歉
They left. I'm sorry.
是你的男朋友?
- Was that your boyfriend? - No.
你没有男朋友是么?
- You don't have a boyfriend? - No.
那么 他是谁呢?
Well, who was it?
我和他 反正已经走了
I was.... He's gone.
我是说 我们根本 总之现在没事了 好吗?
I mean, it's not- lt's over, you know?
介意我四处检查一下吗?
You mind if I have a look around for your safety?
- 可以的 - 好
- lt's fine. - Okay.
你想要找什么啊?
Uh, what- ? What are you looking for?
克劳迪娅 应该是我来问你问题
Claudia, why don't you let me handle the questions...
你来好好回答 好么?
- ...and you handle the answers, okay? - Okay.
我是来帮你的
- I'm here to help you. - Okay.
- 你现在还有做作业吗? - 不像以前那么多了
- So do you still have to do homework? - Not as much as I used to.
从我们参赛后 我就很少去学校了
Since we started, I haven't gone to school much.
- 我得参加一堆试演 - 我一直没有去上课
- I've had so many auditions. - I don't have regular classes anymore.
- 那你做些什么? - 他们给我自己时间学习
- What do you do? - They let me have my own study time.
- 自己在图书馆阅读 - 真酷
- My own reading time in the library. - That's pretty cool.
- 你有经纪人了么? - 没有
- Do you have an agent, Stanley? - No.
你应该找一个 我是说真的 能帮你做不少事呢
You should get one. I'm serious. You could get a lot of stuff out of this.
- 比如什么? - 什么比如什么?比如签些狗屁协议什么的
- Like what? - What do you mean? Endorsements and shit!
- 理查德 - 得了吧 辛西娅
- Richard. - Bite it, Cynthia.
你可以得到很多美事 一旦大家开始喜欢认同你
You get stuff from people that want you to endorse their product.
就有机会拍广告 演连续剧 或者MOW什么的
Commercials, a sitcom, an M.O.W. or something.
- 什么是MOW? - 就是周末电影
- What's M.O.W.? - Hello. Movie of the week.
我今天参加了一个试镜 里面有阿兰・塞克和克里・海姆
I went for one this morning with Alan Thicke and Corey Haim.
- 通过了吗? - 无所谓 不过应该通过了
RlCHARD: Was it a callback? JULlA: No, but I'll probably get a callback.
如果今天我们破纪录 你肯定会通过的
RlCHARD: lf we beat the record, you might get a callback.
我通过是因为我演技很棒 懂么 理查德
JULlA: I'll get it because I'm a good actress, Richard.
- 哟 哟! - 好了 你们
- RlCHARD: Saucy, saucy. - CYNTH lA: Come on, guys. Settle down.
- 辛西娅? - 你想怎么样?
- Cynthia? - What do you want?
- 我得去下洗手间 - 不能忍忍么?
- I gotta go to the bathroom. - CYNTH lA: Can you hold it?
各位 哇哦
Yessiree! Whoa!
新的奇迹就要出现了 非常谢谢大家
That was absolutely fantastic, and I thank you very much.
事实上 你们将与我一起见证这次
As a matter of fact, we may even take you folks on the road with us.
- 这是我的事 - 别这样 我是说真的
LUlS: That's my thing. Come on. I'm serious. Come on.
乳品和竞技 你们从没听过乳品和竞技吗?
Milk and sports, man. You never heard- ? Milk and sports, okay?
随便什么球类比赛 或者涉及到比分的
Anything baseball. Um, anything dealing with numbers...
就是到了要打破什么纪录的时候
...when it comes to those, you know, or who broke whatever record.
随便日常生活中的吃法
Any kind of dairy product, any kind- Dairy recipe...
比如 山羊奶 羊乳酪 随便这样的都行
...um, like goat milk, goat cheese, goat- All that stuff.
不信这次试试看
Wow, check this out over here.
好吗? 伙计们 和我一起试吧
So, um, look guys, just work with me on that. Work with me.
不好意思 给我拿杯低脂奶好么?
Excuse me, can you bring me low- fat milk, please?
再来些冰块
A couple of ice cubes.
他们看起来也不是很强
Ah, they don't look so tough.
看上去很聪明吗?
Do they look smart? - No.
- 他们以为能赢吗?想赢我们? - 也许吧
- RlCHARD: What are they gonna do, beat us? - Maybe.
为了这个纪录 我已经两天没出门了
We're not going out two days before we set the record.
这不会发生的
lt's not gonna happen.
他们想让我们完蛋
RlCHARD: Yeah. When they want us done...
他们叫来了哈佛的SWAT队
...they'll call in the Harvard SWAT team or some shit.
要开始啦
Ready to run.
- 你看起来不太好 - 我顶得住
You smell like trouble. - I'm fucking hammered.
- 真的没事? - 你知道
- You okay? - You know.
好 那先检查一遍好么?
Good. You have a chance to look those over?
我都他妈的检查了三十年了 伯特
Oh, come on. lt's the same fucking shit for 30 years, Burt.
你装得挺有钱的样子
You look like you have money in your pocket.
可能我是见到我的好布拉德后太高兴了吧
Maybe I'm just happy to see my friend Brad there.
扔你的破钱吧
DONNlE: Just throw some money around.
- 钱 钱 钱 - 是布拉德
- Money, money, money. - lt's Brad.
你来找茬的吗?
Ooh. This sounds threatening.
你心中有 爱 这东西吗?
Do you have love in your heart?
我心中充满了爱
I have love all over.
我甚至对你都赋予了爱 朋友
I even have love for you, friend.
- 你这就叫爱么? - 呃
- ls it real love? - Well-
这就敢称作那种让你
The kind of love that makes you feel that intangible joy...
心中充满难以名状的喜悦
...in the pit of your stomach...
一种酸酸麻麻的感觉袭遍全身
...like a bucket of acid and nerves running around...
让你倾倒让你兴奋 不知所以
...and making you hurt and happy and all over...?
你觉得你真懂爱么?
You're head over heels?
我听不懂你那些故作高深的词儿
You lost me with the last couple of cocktail words spoken, my boy...
但是我相信我有爱
...but I believe it's that sort of love.
我喜欢这样
Sounds nice to me.
我有爱
I have love.
嗯 你很会说话 真的
Hmm, a very chatty kind. lndeed you do, it seems.
不是 我很认真的
No, I mean, I'm telling you.
我有爱
I'm telling you, I have love.
是啊 我在洗耳恭听啊 哥们
Yes, and I'm listening avidly, fellow.
我就是丹尼尔・史密斯 我现在满腔爱意要倾泻
My name is Donnie Smith, and I have lots of love to give.
- 你好 - 嗨
- Hello. - Hi.
喔
Wow.
还真不少 哈?
Lot of stuff here, huh?
还有三十秒
lt's 30 seconds.
稍等片刻 就来
- eye on you. I'll be back.
- 嗨 辛西娅 - 杰克 杰克
- Hi, Cynthia. - Jakety, Jakety.
他妈的那边是怎么回事?
RlCHARD: The fuck is going on over there?
- 我要去洗手间 - 怎么回事啊你 斯坦利
- I gotta go to the bathroom. - Jesus Christ, Stanley.
不 不 不 你不应该这么做 我来教教你们
No, no, no. You cannot do that. Let me explain something to you people.
你要学会和他进行调解 被老是那么凶巴巴的
You have to tone it. Don't be real aggressive like that.
你要巧妙地用些手段来 让他自己解决
Be subtly abusive so they don't know what's happening.
噢不 你不能出去玩儿
You say, You're not gonna go outside and play with your friends...
除非房间都干干净净了才行
...until that entire room is cleaned floor to ceiling.
茱莉亚的房间也是那样儿
Oh, Julia's room's the same way.
跟猪圈似的 不过现在好了
JULlA'S DAD: Like a pigsty. But it's the outfits we're into now.
你们根本想不到这孩子出门时 穿成什么样子!
Oh, you should have seen what she had on walking out the door.
我告诉她 不 你是去上学 不是去时装秀
I said, No. We're going to school, not a fashion show.
不是去时装秀 是去上学
RlCHARD'S MOM: lt's not a fashion show. lt's school.
当然了 这不是时装秀
JULlA'S MOM: Absolutely. lt's not a fashion show.
嘘
Shh.
要开始了 伙计们 要开始了
Let's make some fucking money here, people.
吉米 你没事吧 吉米?
You with me, Jimmy?
书上说 虽然时过境迁
JlMMY: The book says, We may be through with the past...
但我们不会改变
...but the past ain't through with us.
我们在高处相见 然后在广场上分手
We met upon the level and We met upon the level, and we're parting on the square.
还他妈的是在我睡觉的时候
ln my fucking sleep, Burt.
五 四 三 二 一
And five, four, three, two....
这里是来自加州博班克的现场直播 小孩儿都知道?!
Live from Burbank, California, its What Do Kids Know?
这是我们节目播出第三十三个年头 美国史上最长的一场智力挑战赛
Going into our 33rd year on the air, it's America's longest- running quiz show...
就在这里 三位孩子将与三位成年人展开较量
...and the place where three kids get to challenge three adults...
让我们拭目以待 谁是最后的胜者吧!
...and in the end, we'll see who's the boss.
下面请出连续七周卫冕的
Moving towards their eighth consecutive week as champions...
少年组 他们是理查德 茱莉亚和斯坦利
...we have the kids: Richard, Julia, and Stanley.
和本次挑战者 成年组的米姆 路易斯和陶德
And our new adult challengers today are Mim, Luis, and Todd.
我是迪克・詹宁斯
And me, I'm Dick Jennings...
现在让我们欢迎金牌主持人
...and now say hello to your favorite host and my boss...
吉米・加托
...Jimmy Gator.
好!好!好!我是吉米・加托 真是令人无法相信
Back again, again, again. I'm Jimmy Gator, and believe it or not...
连续七周卫冕成功 即将挑战第八周的
...we are at the end of Week 7, heading towards Week 8...
我们这三位天才少年 你们好!
...with these three incredible kids, who- Hello, hello.
只差两天也就是两场比赛 距离现在的小孩儿都知道的纪录
- are just two days and two games away from the What Do Kids Know? record...
我们的节目是美国电视史上最长的智力比赛
...for the longest- running quiz show in television history.
目前 我们已经得到家庭教师协会
Now, we are, as you know, endorsed by the PTA...
和北美教师基金会的认可
...and the North American Teachers' Foundation.
我们一贯保持节目的制作精良
We keep our standards high, and that's why we are the longest- running quiz show...
因此成就了美国电视史上的辉煌 我想要对孩子们说的是
...in television history. I wanna say something about these kids now.
他们终于达到了今天的成功
These kids right here, I think they're gonna be here a while.
但是今天的卫冕将充满艰辛
But today is a dangerous day...
我刚才在后台与三位成年挑战者交谈过
...because I have just met with the adult challengers backstage...
说实话 他们将是孩子们遇到的最强大的敌人
...and let me tell you, they are a terrific challenge for our kids.
那么 现在就让我们进入比赛吧!
So let's get this show up and away, shall we?
我们想知道你的儿子在哪儿
DETECTlVE: We wanna know where your son is.
这个人是不是曾经和你丈夫打过架? 他外号是蚯蚓吗?
Jerome Samuel Hall. Did he fight your husband? ls this the Worm?
他们或者发生了打斗 或者仅仅是场意外
DETECTlVE: They had a fight. An accident. OFFlCER: They call him Worm?
他外号是叫蚯蚓吗?
DETECTlVE: We wanna know where your son is.
- 我们要知道你儿子在哪里 玛茜 - 他就是蚯蚓吗?
- Help us, Marcie. - Do they call him Worm?
- 告诉我们 对你孩子有好处的 玛茜 - 他就是蚯蚓吗?
- Help us help your son, Marcie. - OFFlCER: Do they call him Worm?
帮我们也帮你儿子
DETECTlVE: Help us help your son, Marcie.
你的儿子 还有你孙子 说出来吧 想想他们
OFFlCER: Your son and your grandson. Help us help them.
这就是蚯蚓么?
ls this the Worm?
进入正题
JlMMY Let's jump right in.
简单介绍一下比赛规则
A quick recap for those who don't know.
第一轮将有三种类型
Round One. Three categories. Steals are okay.
分值从25到250不等 其中包括连续谈话奖励
Point scale escalating from 25 to 250, one of which is a conversation bonus.
- 一共是 31 90 - 嗨
- Hi. - That'll be 31.90.
题型非别为 回答作者身份和配乐题
The categories are authors, chaos versus superstring, and rub- a- dub.
- 刚刚好 谢谢 - 再见
- Max. Thanks. - Bye.
成年组掷硬币是反面 因此他们将先回答
Adults won a coin toss backstage, so they get to pick first.
队长是 米姆
Team captain: Mim.
第一题 25分
First question, for 25.
这位女作家最著名的作品为《啊!拓荒者》
This female author's most famous work: O Pioneers!
是H- E- R
PHlL: H- E- R
- 斯坦利 - 薇拉・卡瑟
- JlMMY: Stanley? - Willa Cather.
薇拉・卡瑟 25分!
Willa Cather for 25.
作为著名的悲剧大师 这位剧作家
Best known for the tragedy- of- blood genre, this playwright-
- 斯坦利 - 托马斯・基德
- Stanley. - Thomas Kyd.
托马斯・基德
Thomas Kyd.
这位法国剧作家兼演员曾在贝雅尔剧团
This French playwright and actor joined the Bejart troupe of actors-
- 斯坦利 - 莫里哀
- Stanley. - Moliere.
你得告诉我他的全名 斯坦利
Oh, I'm afraid I'm gonna need a full name, Stanley.
简・巴蒂斯特・帕邱林・莫里哀
Jean Baptiste Poquelin Moliere.
这叫什么事儿啊!?
What the fuck is this?
干得漂亮!这小兔崽子!哈哈哈
God damn. My little fucker. Ha- ha- ha!
他都从哪儿记的这些玩意儿!真他妈是个天才
I have no idea where he gets this shit. He's a fucking genius, really.
《诱惑与征服》 我是查德
Seduce and Destroy. This is Chad.
能告诉我你的号码吗?
Can I have your phone number?
- 是《诱惑与征服》么? - 是的 能告诉我你号码么?
- ls this Seduce and Destroy? - Yes, it is. Can I have your phone number?
好 我不想要求什么 呃 你知道
Okay, I don't want to order anything. Uh, you see....
我这里有点事情 非常棘手的一件事
I have a situation, uh, that's just come up that's really pretty serious...
我现在不知道该找谁 该怎么做
...and I don't know who to talk to or what I should do...
不过也许你能帮我找到那人 我应该先解释一下是吗?
...but maybe you could put me in touch with somebody if I explain myself?
我们这里只是受理订单的啊 先生
Uh, we're really only equipped to take orders here, sir.
我们在电话里只能谈和工作有关的
I mean, it's just us with the phones, and that's what we do, you know-
你能够帮我转到另外哪位的电话上么?
Okay, okay, okay. Could you connect me with somebody else, you think?
发生了什么?
Well, what's the situation?
好吧 听我讲
Okay, great, um....
我来解释一下整件事 才不会让你糊里糊涂
All right. Let me try to explain myself without it seeming crazy.
听我讲
But here I go. I'm- No.
我叫菲尔・帕尔马
Uh, my name is Phil Parma...
我替一个叫厄尔・帕特里奇的人工作
...and I work for, uh, a man named Earl Partridge.
嗯 厄尔・帕特里奇先生
Uh, Mr. Earl Partridge.
我是他的护理 他病得非常重
I'm his nurse, and he's a very sick man.
快要不行了 他已经非常虚弱了
He's a dying man, and he's sick...
他请求我帮助他
...and he has asked me to help him.
帮他寻找他的儿子
To help him find his son.
- 喂?你还在吗? - 在 正在听
- Hello? Are you there? Hello? - No, I'm here. I'm listening.
好 是这样
Okay. Um, you see...
就是厄尔・帕特里奇的儿子
...Frank T.J. Mackey is Earl Partridge's son.
你来自哪里?
So where are you from originally?
- 就是这里 - 就这一带么?
- From around here. - Valley?
- 大概是好莱坞那边 - 你的父母是做什么的呢?
- Well, Hollywood, mainly. - What did your parents do?
我的父亲在电视台工作 我的母亲
Uh, my father- Well, he was in television. My mother-
- 说起来很尴尬 - 告诉我
- This is going to sound silly to you. - Try me.
- 她是位图书馆管理员 - 怎么会觉得尴尬呢?
- Uh, she was a librarian. - Why does that sound silly?
不知道 或许也不会啦
I don't know. I guess it doesn't.
- 你的母亲还在工作么? - 不 她已经退休了
- Does your mother still work? - No, she's retired.
- 你们关系好么? - 她是我的母亲啊
- Are you close? - She's my mother.
是啊 不过 她也是一位女性啊
Yes, but, uh, I mean, she's a woman too...
我是说 她对你的《诱惑与征服》怎么看?
...so how does she feel about Seduce and Destroy?
怎么评价?
I mean, what does she say?
好吧 她说 去做你的吧 亲爱的
Well, she says, uh, You go get them, honey.
那你父亲怎么说?
Uh- huh. And what about your father?
我父亲 哦 很不幸 他已经去世了
Oh, my father. Unfortunately, he passed away.
- 非常抱歉 我无意的 - 不 没关系
- Oh, I'm sorry. I had no idea. - No, please.
我不该问这个的
I wouldn't have brought that up if I had known.
- 这对你太残酷了 - 拜托
- That's a very hard thing. - Please.
没关系的 是的 很残酷 不过 听着
Yes, it is, but listen.
还是应该往前看 过去的终究已经过去了
I mean, you have to move forward. The past has its place.
- 已经很久以前的事了 生老病死 - 是
- lt was a long time ago, and people die. - Yeah.
我们换个话题吧
Okay, let's switch gears here. Um...
根据你书里写的 你毕业于伯克里大学是么?
According to your book, you ended up at UC Berkeley?
对 84年到89年
'84 to '89.
- 心理专业 - 没错
- Psychology major. - That's right.
- 没完成硕士? - 嗯?哦
- Get your masters? - Hmm? Oh.
- 差这么一点儿 - 噢
- This close. - Wow.
- 在校园的五年生活非常难忘是吧 - 伙计 来杯咖啡好么?
- That's impressive in five years. - Cap, can I have some coffee?
我能帮到你吗?
Can I get you anything?
- 不不不 我很好 谢谢 - 你确定?好吧
- No, no, no, I'm good. Thank you. - You sure? Okay.
- 她要很好 我要咖啡 - 哈哈
- She's good. I need coffee. - Ha, ha.
东西还真不少啊 是吧?
PHARMAClST: Cats and dogs out there, huh?
得好几个人得病了吧?
Must have a lot going on for all that stuff back there, huh?
你能
You could, uh...
这些药真会让你无所不能啊
Heh. You could have quite a party, all that stuff.
你用波萨克很久了么? 中枢神经刺激剂呢?
You been on Prozac long? Dexedrine?
- 我不 - 真厉害
- I don't.... - lnteresting drugs.
知道么 中枢神经刺激剂主要是起加速剂作用的
Dexedrine's basically speed in a pill, you know.
但我觉得大多数医生决不会将这两种配在一起
I guess a lot of the doctors are balancing out the Prozac with the Dexedrine, so....
这种液体吗啡将会把你立刻放倒
That liquid morphine will knock you down, out...
毫无知觉 如果一旦不用不当的话
...around, up and down, someone's not careful.
怎么能将它们混在一起呢
You can't mix those up, you know.
强得吓死人啊 我说
Strong, strong stuff here, boy. Wow!
你到底有什么问题 竟然需要这些玩意儿?
What you have wrong, you need all this stuff?
- 畜牲! - 什么?
- Motherfucker. - What?
- 他妈的畜牲! - 你说什么?
- Motherfucker. You fucking asshole. - What are you talking about?
- 你以为你他妈的是谁啊? - 我只是
- Who the fuck do you think you are? - I'm just trying-
我来这里 你根本就不知道我是谁 要做什么
I come in here. You don't know me. You don't know who I am, what my life is...
你就敢这么恬不知耻地向我问这问那?
...and you have the balls, the indecency to ask me a question about my life?
- 夫人 别激动好么? - 还有你这个混蛋 不许你叫我夫人!
- Please, lady, calm down. - Fuck you too! Don't you call me lady!
我进来这里 我把处方交给你们
I come in here, I give these things to you...
你们竟然要检查 还打电话
...you check, you make your phone calls...
还要怀疑 还要问这问那!
...look suspicious, ask questions.
我受不了了!
I'm sick.
我的一切都要完蛋了 你们竟然还向我问这问那?
I have sickness all around me, and you fucking ask me my life?
到底想怎么样?
What's wrong?
没在床上见过死人吗?在你家里!?
Have you seen death in your bed? ln your house?
装什么狗屁正经?还想逼我回答你们的狗屁问题
Where's your fucking decency? And then I'm asked fucking questions.
想要干什么?!
What's wrong?
让我操了你! 你想要这个是吧!
You suck my dick, that's what's wrong.
还有你 也他妈配叫我夫人?
And you. You fucking call me lady?
你这个臭不要脸的!
Shame on you!
你们两个臭不要脸的
Shame on you. Shame on both of you.
那么他们为什么不同姓呢?
Why don't they have the same last name?
因为你看 他们姓氏不一样诶
Because they don't have the same last name.
我知道 但是很难解释清楚 不过
PHlL: I know, and I can't really explain that, but I think-
我感觉他们之间发生过什么事情
I have a feeling there is something, you know, a situation between them...
可能互相不能很好地理解对方
...like they don't know each other much or well, you know?
之后两人再也没有过联系了
Something like they don't talk much anymore, even.
嗯嗯
Uh- huh.
天哪 听起来很怪异是吧?
You know? God, does this sound weird?
我只是一直不明白你为什么会打给我呢
Ha, ha. I just don't understand why you're calling me.
厄尔的家里找不到关于弗兰克的任何信息
Well, there's no number for Frank in any of EarI's stuff...
他也快不长了
...you know, and he's pretty out of it.
我说了 他已经不行了
I mean, like I said, he's dying.
被癌症 嗯
Dying of cancer. So...
- 什么癌? - 脑和肺
- What kind of cancer? - lt's brain and lung.
- 我母亲得过乳癌 - 对不起
- My mother had breast cancer. - Oh, I'm sorry.
- 现在好了是么? - 对 现在好了
- ls she all right? - Oh, she's fine now.
- 太好了 - 不过还是吓死人了当时
- Oh, that's good. - lt was scary, though.
- 这种病真的是害死人 - 真的是这样
- Oh, it's a hell of a disease. - Oh, it sure is.
- 对 - 好吧 嗯
- Yeah. - Well, so, uh...
对了 真抱歉 到底为什么给我打电话来着?
Wait, I'm sorry. So why call me?
我知道这么做很傻 也很荒唐
I know this sounds silly, and I know that I might sound ridiculous...
装得好像是电影一样
...like this is the scene of the movie...
老人希望能见失散多年孩子的最后一面
...where the guy is trying to get ahold of the long- lost son...
但是这真的和现在一模一样
...you know, but this is that scene. This is that scene.
我觉得 他们之所以会把这种故事写进电影
And I think they have those scenes in movies...
就因为它们在现实中是真实发生着的
...because they're true, you know.
它们真的在发生着
Because they really happen.
你一定要相信我 千真万确的
And you gotta believe me, this is really happening.
我把我号码给你 你可以去检查
I mean, I can give you my number and you can go check...
随便怎么检查都行 只要给我回电话就好
...with whoever you gotta check with...
千万请别让我傻傻地等着
...but do not leave me hanging on this.
好吗? 拜托啦 我实在 求你了
All right? Please. I'm just- Please.
觉得
See....
这真像电影里面的情节不是么? 最后的拯救的那种
See, this is, uh, the scene of the movie where you help me out.
你挺厉害 你这些问题很漂亮
You're great. These are great questions.
- 谢谢 很好 - 真的很好
- GWENOVlER: Thank you. Good, good. - This is going great.
好吧 我认为你是在这一带长大的
See, I thought you grew up here in the Valley.
是啊 我刚才说过 这一带
Yeah. You know, like I said. Around.
你去过拜占庭高中?
You went to Van Nuys High, right?
我不止上过 我当时天天上
I wouldn't say I went. I frequented.
教得相当烂 我当时绝对不像现在的弗兰克・T・J・麦吉
I was misguided, pathetic. Not the Frank T.J. Mackey...
不是现在这个你拼命想曝光的弗兰克
...you're so eagerly, uh, wanting to put on national television.
我当时选择了完全不适合我的人生方向
Because I was swimming in what was as opposed to what I wanted.
- 你的姓是怎么来的? - 我的姓?
- Where does that name come from? - What name? My name?
这不是你的本姓吧?
Yeah. lt's not your given name, right?
实际上 这是我妈妈的姓 干得漂亮 继续审问我吧
lt's my mother's name, actually. That's good. Good. Done your research.
- 那名字弗兰克呢? - 是我外祖父的
- And Frank? - Frank is my mother's father.
事实上 是这样 我遇到了些困难
Oh, okay. That's why. See, I had some trouble...
当我要查你在加州大学洛杉矶分校和伯克里的注册纪录时
...locating your school records at, um, UCLA and, uh, Berkeley.
可能是因为你换名字 因为他们没有你的正式注册纪录
And it's your name change. See, they had no official enrollment for you.
- 不不不他们不会有的 - 不会?
- No, no, no, they wouldn't. - They wouldn't?
不会的 因为我本来就没有正式注册过
No, because I was never officially enrolled there.
- 还不清楚么? - 有点
- Was that unclear? - Kind of.
拜托 我可不希望有误解
Oh. God, I wouldn't want that to be misunderstood.
我当时不算正规就读
No, uh, my enrollment was totally unofficial.
当时很可怜 付不起它们的学费
Sadly, I couldn't afford to pay the tuition up there.
不过有三个非常优秀的教授 热情地让我听他们的课
There were three wonderful professors who let me to sit in their classes.
他们是麦克里迪 霍恩和兰特里
Their names were Macready, Horn, and Langtree, among others.
需要的话你可以给他们打电话 我成功的并不轻松
You're welcome to call them if you like. See, I didn't get a free ride...
你非常喜欢研究我那些琐碎的过去
...so, what we're looking at here is a true rags- to- riches story.
这就是现在人们对我的征服学说兴趣如此之大
That's why people respond so strongly to Seduce...
因为在当今的年代 征服不仅仅局限于
...because at the end of the day, Seduce may not be just...
分开她双腿插进去占有她
...about picking up chicks, sticking your cock in.
而是一种对你能成为何种角色的暗示
lt's about finding out what you can be in this world...
告诉自己 驾驭自己 对自己暗示 我会拿到属于我的东西
...defining it, controlling it, and saying, I will take what is mine.
可能仅仅是迫切地想要一场口交而已
And you happen to get a little blow job out of it...
- 总之 嘿 管他妈是什么呢 - 哈哈 没错
- ...then, hey, what the fuck? Why not? - Ha, ha, okay. There you go.
第一回合结束 都很棒
End of Round One. Excellent work, ladies and germs.
现在应该来看看两队的比分了
I think we should take a look at the scores here.
少年组1 500分 稍稍领先
Kids are up a leg with 1500...
成年组紧随其后 是1025分
...and the adults are down a little bit with 1025.
我们马上进入第二回合 最后进入叮叮咚!
So we'll be back for Round Two in a ring- ding- do.
现在是额外奖励的音乐题目
Whoa, hello, hello. Bonus musical question.
参加者将是
And the winner is...
少年组!
...kids.
他们目前领先 并且将有机会拉大距离
Uh, kids are in the lead. They get a chance to pull further ahead...
只要他们能答对这道额外的音乐题
...if they can answer the following secret- bonus musical question.
好 我现在要念某部歌剧中的一句唱词
Now, what I'm going to do is read a line from an opera.
我要你们重新唱这句词
Give me that line back...
用歌剧原作语言来念出来
...in the language in which the opera was written...
如果想要多加250 250 250分的话
...and for a bonus 250- Um, 250- Uh, 250...
你要把它唱出来!
...uh, you can sing it. Heh.
下面是唱词
Here's the line.
爱情就是一只无人能驯服的倔强的鸟儿
Love is a rebellious bird that nobody can tame...
若它不理睬你 什么样的呼唤都会是徒劳无功
...and it's all in vain to call it if it chooses to refuse.
对 斯坦利
Yes, Stanley.
嗯 这句是从法语翻译过来的
Well, that was in French...
它是出自歌剧卡门
...and that was from the opera Carmen...
是这样唱的
...and that goes:
你这儿刚煮了些咖啡啊
- You got some coffee brewing here. CLAUDlA: lt's not-
是的 不是刚煮 放很久了
lt's been on for a bit.
我喜欢喝冰咖啡的 平时
Yeah, I like iced coffee, generally...
不过像今天这样的 下着雨什么的日子里
...but a day like today, you know, with the rain and whatnot...
我喜欢热乎乎的来上一杯
... I enjoy a warm cup.
要来一杯吗?
Do you want a cup?
方便吗?外面正下得稀里糊涂的
ls that all right? Just raining cats and dogs out there.
我恐怕还真不想立刻就出去 呵呵
I'd just as soon not go back in it. Heh.
我不知道这喝起来会是什么样子
I don't know how fresh it's gonna be.
肯定没事儿的 克劳迪娅
Oh, I'm sure it's fine, Claudia.
你要奶油和糖么?
Do you, um, take cream or sugar?
可以啊 嗯
That would be fine. Um-
好吧 克劳迪娅 我得把话说完 这样我才算完成巡警的职责
So, Claudia, let me just say, so I can get my role as an LAPD officer...
在我们喝咖啡之前说完
...out of the way before we enjoy our coffee.
我不喜欢喝咖啡时板着脸喝
I don't like to talk shop over coffee.
我不会把你写进纪录
I'm not gonna write you up.
我也不会向局里报告你这里的
I'm not gonna give you a citation here...
不过问题是这样 周围的住着其他人
...but the real problem we have here is that you got people around you...
那些下班回家的 累了一天终于想休息一下的人们
...people who work from home trying to get some work done...
而你要是老这么大声音听音乐的话 会给他们造成很大不便
...and if you're listening to your music that loud, they're inconvenienced by that.
如果你工作过的话 应该不难理解这些
lf you had a job, you'd probably understand, but...
当然 你喜欢听你的音乐 这没什么错
You like listening to your music. That's fine. That's fine. Um....
只是希望你能注意一下音量
You're just gonna wanna keep an eye on the volume level.
或许可以记住音量旋钮的刻度
You know, maybe memorize what number you see on the dial.
如果中午时我要听音乐 我就是这么调的
lf it's the middle of the day, that's what I do.
我把它旋到二又二分之一处 以后我就记住了这是我听音乐的最佳音量
...I set it at two and a half, and then I know that's a good listening level for me.
你就是喜欢开得太大声了
But, uh, you like listening to your music loud.
挺好的 挺酷的 有些时候是需要一些发泄吧
That's fine. That's cool. lt's good to rock out sometimes.
不过你还是不应该天天这样啊
But you can't do it every day...
否则真的会让你听力受损伤的 真的
...or else you risk damaging your ears. Seriously.
- 你每次听音乐都拧这么大吗? - 是的
- You listen to it all the time like that? - Yeah.
你会把周围人们气疯的
You're gonna drive these people crazy.
好吧 听懂了么?
Anyway, you get the point.
- 懂了 - 好
- Yes. - Okay.
嗯
Um...
谢谢
Cheers.
- 嗯 男朋友气你了? - 我没有男朋友
- So this boyfriend bothering you? - I don't have a boyfriend.
- 那个门口的男士 - 他不是我男朋友
- The gentleman who was at the door- - He's not my boyfriend.
通常情况下 家庭内部充满压力时
Okay. A lot of times, in domestic- abuse situations...
年轻的女孩子都害怕把他说出来
...the young woman is afraid to speak out.
不过你不用害怕讲给我听
You don't have to be afraid to tell me anything.
而且作为一名警察 我可以告诉你
And as a police officer, I can tell you...
这样会更糟
...it goes bad places.
女孩子们害怕说出来 还有 知道么 这就是187号
Young woman is afraid, next thing you know, I'm here on a 187.
什么187号?
lt's not- What's a 187?
这样真的不好 就是代表这样类似的情况
lt's not good. And it's where situations like this always lead.
不是我男朋友 什么都不是
lt's not my boyfriend, and it's not anything.
都结束了 真的 不会再来了
lt's over. Really. lt's not. He won't come back.
- 我可不想在跑过来 - 不会的!
- I don't wanna have to come back here- - You won't have to.
我并不是说不想再来
You know, l- I wouldn't mind coming back.
再来 看看你漂亮的脸儿
You know, get a look at your pretty face again.
失陪一下
I'll be right back.
给你水
Here you go.
我帮你把外套脱掉 好让你舒服点儿
Let's get the jacket off. lt will help you to breathe.
我做不下去了
I can't fucking do this.
我 我
I've, uh-
我觉得我要吐了 恐怕
I think- I'm gonna throw up, I think.
我二十岁后就没吐过了
I haven't thrown up since I was 20 years old.
辛西娅
Cynthia.
你是个男人
You are the man.
- 怎么啦? - 我要去洗手间
- What's the problem? - I need to go to the bathroom.
哦 斯坦利 现在不行
Jesus Christ, Stanley. You can't go now.
离开始就剩一分钟了
You have one minute before we're on the air.
现在可不是去洗手间的时候!
Now is not the time to go to the bathroom.
- 你犯什么病了 斯坦利? - 嘿
RlCHARD: Why does this always happen? - Hey.
我说 出什么事儿啦?
Excuse me, is there a problem over there?
干你屁事儿!
Mind your own business.
- 怎么说话的 这孩子! - 管好你自己吧!
- You better watch your mouth. - Why don't you mind your own business?
- 哦不 她没有 - 冷静下来 拜托
- LUlS: Oh, no, she didn't. - CooI down. Cool it, please.
忍到插播广告就能去了 好么?
Now, Stanley, wait for the commercial break, then you can go.
- 再忍一下 - 他们那里找的这些熊孩子
- Just hold it. - LUlS: Where did they get these kids?
别说孩子们了
Don't taunt the kids.
- 我只是想看能帮点什么而已 - 别挑事了
- I'm trying to be helpful. - CYNTH lA: Don't start trouble, Luis.
哪儿有什么事儿啊! 等会儿插广告了再说
Honey, you haven't seen trouble. Wait till next commercial break.
- 怎么了? - 没事儿
- What's the problem? - Nothing.
莉莉! 快来! 来!
Lily! Please!
订购《诱惑与征服》
FRANK: Order Seduce and Destroy...
- 滚开 你这个狗屎! - 好
- Get away from me, you shithead! - Okay.
买不起? 我们将努力为您服务
Can't afford it? We'll work out something for you.
《诱惑与征服》 将改变你的生活
Seduce and Destroy will change your life.
当心 当心
Watch out, watch out, watch out.
不
No.
不要 不要
Don't, don't, don't.
- 我来救你 - 喂 喂?好
- I'm gonna save you. - Hi? Hello? Okay.
我保证 钱如数奉还
I guarantee, money- back guarantee-
- 别吃了 - 它将改变你的生活
- Don't eat these. - This will change your life.
它会帮助你
It's gonna help you get that naughty sauce that you...
- 对于一个成本是49块9毛9 - 来了
- For a low cost of 49.99... - PHlL: Here you go.
出来吧 和《诱惑与征服》一起
Come on out of the cold and order Seduce and Destroy...
49块9毛9的低成本 可以使用任何信用卡支付
...for the low cost of 49.99. We take all credit cards.
- 维萨卡 万事达卡 - 从垃圾桶里出来
- I take Visa, MasterCard... - PHlL: Out of the trash, out of the trash.
嘿 菲尔在么?
Hey, Phil, are you there?
- 我是查德 - 嗨 查德
- lt's Chad. - Yeah. Hi, Chad.
我要把电话转给珍妮特 她是弗兰克的助理
Yeah, listen, I'm gonna put you in touch with Janet, Frank's assistant.
- 好 - 让她看看该怎么处理
- Okay. - And she's gonna see what she can do.
谢谢你 祝你好运 还有你的母亲
Thank you very much, and good luck to you and your mother.
谢谢 你也是 好的 珍妮特 还在吗?
Thanks, man. You too. Okay, Janet, are you there?
- 喂? - 好了 珍妮特 这里是菲尔・帕尔马
- Hello? - All right, Janet, you have Phil Parma.
好吗?
Okay?
我得了癌症 玛莉 已经两个月了
I have cancer, Mary. I have about two months.
没多少日子了
I have no time.
晚期了 我没得选择
lt's in my bones. I don't have a chance.
- 哦 - 我玩儿完了
- Oh. - I'm fucked.
- 还有十五秒 - 你有什么曲奇或者其他东西吗?
- DlRECTOR: And 15 seconds. - LUlS: You got any cookies or anything?
十秒
DlRECTOR: Ten seconds.
五 四 三 二
And five, four, three, two....
回到现场 进入第二回合!
We're back, ready for Round Two.
让我问问今天参赛的成人组选手们
We're talking to our adult contestants here today.
米姆 资料说你来自加州的查茨沃思
Uh, Mim, it says here that you live in California...
你有两个孩子
...and that you have two kids.
没错 我有一个六岁的
MlM: Right. I have a six- year- old son...
知道我是谁么?
Do you know who I am?
你是我们大家庭里的一员 我猜
You're a friend of the family, I presume.
什么意思?
What does that mean?
没什么 玩转生活
Nothing special. Just a spoke in the wheel.
你以为自己说得挺文雅挺有层次
You talk in rhymes and riddles and rub- a- dub...
其实对我来说什么都不是 知道么 我曾经很聪明
...but that doesn't mean anything to me. See, see- See, I used to be smart.
我就是神童 丹尼尔・史密斯
I'm Quiz Kid Donnie Smith.
我就是电视里那个神童 丹尼尔・史密斯
I'm Quiz Kid Donnie Smith from TV.
恐怕很早以前真是吧
lt might have been before my time.
我记得你 六零年那会儿 对吧?
I remember now. ln the sixties, right?
- 我就是天才少年丹尼尔・史密斯 - 如你所说
- I'm Quiz Kid Donnie Smith. - Like you said.
天才少年 你曾经被闪电劈过吧?
Smart kid. You got struck by lightning at one time, right?
怎么啦?
DONNlE: So what?
- 我听说过 - 当时疼吗?
- I heard about that. - Did it hurt?
很疼
DONNlE: Yes.
但你现在很正常啊 到底怎么搞的
But you're all right now. So, what's the what?
- 什么? - 没什么
- What? - That's right.
我曾经那么聪明 现在却是个傻瓜
I used to be smart. Now I'm just stupid.
布拉德 亲爱的 是谁曾经说过来者
Ha! Brad, dear, who was it that said:
一个天才决不会因为毁于自己的手中?
A man of genius has seldom been ruined but by himself?
嗯
Um...
- 是可爱的塞缪尔・约翰逊 - 啊
The lovely Samuel Johnson. - Ah.
这个谁又接着说 那么他不仅自己愚笨
Who also spoke of a fellow who was not only dull...
更会令大家变得愚笨?
...but a cause of dullness in others.
更会愚笨大家
DONNlE: The cause of dullness in others.
- 是啊 是啊! - 我来告诉你
- Picky, picky. - Let me tell you this.
塞缪尔・约翰逊从来没有过这种破日子
Samuel Johnson never had his life shit on...
让别人把他钱拿走 偷走!
...and taken from him, and his money stolen.
谁抢走了他的人生和金钱?
Who took his life and his money?
他家长? 他妈妈和爸爸?
His parents? His mommy and daddy?
规定他过着这样的生活
Make him live this life like this.
一个从小过着这种狗屁日子的有天赋的人
A man of genius who gets shit on as a child...
会留下伤痕的!非常痛苦的!
...and that scars. That hurts.
你到底有没有被闪电击过?
Have you ever been hit by lightning?
很痛的 并不是每个人都能经历
lt hurts. lt doesn't happen to everyone.
那是一种充电
lt's an electrical charge.
它穿过宇宙找到了自己的方向
lt finds its way across the universe...
然后落在你身上 落在你头上!
...and it lands in your body and your head.
然后 之后就这么毁了 被他自己
And as for ruined but by himself...
要不是他父母强加着这种畸形的人生
...not if his parents took his freaking life...
还抢走他的钱 还命令你做这个
...and his money, and tell you to do this...
做那个 如果你不做的话
...and to do that, and if you don't, well....
你父母拿走了你比赛赢的奖金?
Your parents took your money that you won on that game show?
是的! 拿走了
Yes. They did.
那是什么意思来着 玩转生活?
What does that mean, a spoke in the wheel?
生活这么一天天转着 不是么?
Things go round and round, don't they?
是的 转着 转着
Yes, they do. They do.
但我要实现我的梦
But I'll make my dreams come true.
听起来垂头丧气的
Sounds sad as a weeping willow.
我曾经那么聪明
I used to be smart.
现在却是个傻瓜
But now I'm just stupid.
我们该为此干杯么?
Shall we drink to that?
我想再多谈谈你的家庭背景
Um, I wanna talk a little bit more about your background.
你之前也有说过
You made, um, some references earlier...
经历了一些人生经验 和悲惨的事情
...to, uh, subjective human experiences and terrible things, and, um....
事实上 我对你的过去有一些困惑
Actually, I'm confused about your past, is the thing.
- 这个还没问完啊? - 这很无聊的
- ls that still lingering? lt's so boring. - Just to clarify....
- 只是想把一些地方弄清楚 - 至少 嗯
- Just wanna clear some things up. - Useless. Mm.
打扰了 谢谢 有趣的是
Excuse me. See- Thank you, Muff. lt's a funny thing that-
《诱惑与征服》很重要的一点就是
This is an important element of Seduce and Destroy.
总是沉浸于过去绝对会对你的进步造成阻碍
Facing the past is an important way of not making progress.
我这么告诉我的听众 一次一次又一次
This is something I tell my men over and over and over.
我这并不是
GWENOVlER: This isn't meant, um...
我尝试开导他们问自己
See, I try to teach my students to ask:
这么做为了什么?
What is it in aid of?
- 你是在问我吗? - 是
- Are you asking me that? - Yes.
- 嗯 为了试着弄清楚你到底是 - 为了什么?
- Well, in trying to figure out who you are.... - ln aid of what?
弗兰克 我正在回答啊 是为了搞清你是
Well, Frank, I'm saying that in trying to figure out who you are-
我还有太多更重要的事情
I have more important things...
- 需要投入 - 我想这事就很重要
- ...to put myself into. - Well, no, it's all important.
不妨好好投入想一想
I think this is something important...
可能需要思考的问题 让自己投入进去
...that you might need to think about putting yourself into.
- 不见得 - 嗯 听着 弗兰克
- Mm. Not really. - Um, look, Frank...
我这么做并不是要攻击你
...it's not like I'm trying to attack you here.
- 不 - 我只是
- No. - I just-
你只是想进行你的采访 快 快 快
Okay. Hey, this is how you wanna spend your time, then go, go, go.
不过你马上会发现 这纯粹是浪费时间
But you're gonna be surprised at what a waste it is.
世界上最没有意义的事情 就是回顾过去 第三章
The most useless thing in the world is that which is behind me. Chapter Three.
我们先前谈了你的母亲
We talked earlier about your mother...
你的父亲和他的去世
...and we talked about your father and his death.
我不是想冲撞你 只是想问一问
I don't want to be challenging, but I have to ask, um...
只是想确认一些听来的消息
I just wanna clarify something. Something that I understand...
- 我好像没听到什么问题啊 - 我正在想法子巧妙地问出来
- I'm not sure I hear a question in here. - I'm trying to put this as delicately as I can.
什么问题?
What's the question?
- 还记得西姆斯小姐吗? - 我认识太多女人
- Do you remember a Miss Simms? - I know a lot of women.
- 不过我肯定她还认识我 - 从你还是个孩子时
- I'm sure she remembers me, ha, ha. - She does. From when you were a boy.
- 是吗? - 她就住在塔桑纳
- Yeah? - She lived in Tarzana.
正是我不幸的地方
That's my old stomping ground.
要开始进攻了是么?
ls this the attack portion of the interview?
- 这个女孩要冲进来杀我吗? - 不是的 只是想弄清楚一些事
- ls the girl coming in for the kill? - No. This is about getting something right...
重新澄清你之前的回答的问题
...and clarifying answers to an earlier question.
什么问题?
What question?
我听说你母亲已经不在了 弗兰克
I was told that your mother died, Frank.
你听谁说的
That's what you heard.
那还记得西姆斯小姐么?
Do you remember Miss Simms?
- 不 - 我和西姆斯小姐交谈过
- No. - Well, I talked to Miss Simms...
她是你的邻居还是管理员 就在你母亲1980年去世时
...your neighbor and caretaker after your mother died in 1980...
据我调查
...and in my research...
你原本是厄尔和莉莉帕特里奇・的唯一儿子
... I have you listed as the only son of Earl and Lily Partridge.
而我又从芭芭拉・西姆斯那里听说 你的母亲莉莉
And what I learned from Barbara Simms is that your mother, Lily...
1980年就去世了
...died in 1980.
所以 我猜想之前的信息
So, see, it's my understanding that information supplied...
你和你公司提供的个人信息
...by you and your company...
以及你刚才的回答 都是不真实的
...and the answers to the questions I've asked is incorrect...
我若真想弄清楚你是谁 你为什么要这么做的话
...and if I wanna get to the bottom of who you are and why you are...
那么我想关于你家庭的一些情况 你真实的家庭背景
...then I think that your family history, your actual family history...
嗯 是非常重要的
Well, this is important.
你他妈到底想问什么?
What is your fucking question?
嗯 我想问的就是
Well, I guess my question is this:
你为什么要撒这些谎呢 弗兰克?
Why would you lie, Frank?
少年组 成人组
Kids, adults...
现在是我们轻松的野餐时间
... I would like you to put yourself at a picnic.
你可以叫上你的家人朋友一起享受
Uh, place yourself there with your family and friends, if you'd like.
你们将听到三个音乐代号 你们得告诉我
You'll hear three musical notes, and you are to tell me...
它表示你能在野餐中发现什么
...what it might represent that you would find at a picnic.
第一组 少年组 各位?
The first three notes. Guys?
- 是的 陶德 - 嗯 吉米 我有答案了
- JlMMY: Yes, Todd. - Well, Jimmy, I know this.
我乐感很好的 它们应该是 A- D- E
I have perfect pitch, you see, and that would be A- D- E...
- 代表的应该就是柠檬了 - 加 250 分 下一组 请听
- ...and that would represent lemonade. - JlMMY: For 250. Next notes, please.
- 陶德? - 有了 这是 E- G- G 就是鸡蛋
- JlMMY: Todd? - That's E- G- G, which would be egg.
500分 下面第三组 各位?
JlMMY: For 500. And the third set of notes. Guys?
我快受不了了 阿伦
I'm so fucked up right now, Alan.
- 你不喝水吗? - 不 我只是...
- You don't want any water? - No. l just....
- 全是一团糟 全乱了 - 你是不是嗑药了?
- There's just so much. So many things. - Are you on drugs right now?
我能跟你讲些事情么 你 你是律师 不是么?
lf I tell you something, if I say things, then- You're a lawyer, right?
你不能告诉任何人 就像是保密权 律师和客户之间
You can't say anything, tell anybody. lt's like a privilege. Attorney/client.
- 明白吗? - 不太懂
- You understand? - Not exactly.
就像心理医生那样 看心理医生时 他们就得保密
Like a shrink. lf I go see a shrink, I'm protected.
我就能随便说 操!
I can say things. Oh, fuck.
- 不知道自己到底在干什么 - 琳达 你很安全 没事的
- I don't know what I'm doing. - Linda, you're safe, okay? lt's all right.
你是我的朋友 你和厄尔又是我的客户
You're my friend. You and Earl are clients.
你说什么都决不会传出去的
Whatever you wanna say won't leave this room.
你有事情想要和我说是么?
You have something you wanna say to me....
我有话想告诉你 我想告诉你
I have to tell you something. I have something to tell you.
我想改他的遗嘱 我能改吗? 我需要改
I wanna change his will. Can I change his will? I need to.
不 你不能改他的遗嘱 只有厄尔自己行
No, you can't change his will. Only EarI can.
不不不 听着
No no no You see um
我从来没爱过他
... I never loved him.
我从没爱过厄尔
I never loved him. Earl.
我一见到他 就和他上床 然后就嫁给他
When I met him- When I started- I met him, I fucked him, and I married him...
我只是因为钱 明白么?
...because I wanted his money. You understand?
我说给你这些
Uh, I'm telling you this.
从来没告诉过别人 我以前不爱他
I've never told anyone. Uh, I didn't love him...
但现在 我知道我也在遗嘱中
...but now- I know I'm in that will. We were all there.
那份我们一起写好的遗嘱 我还继承了那么多钱 我不要钱 因为我现在太爱他了
We made that thing. And the money I'll get. I don't want it, because I love him now.
我现在真的太爱他了 他就要死了
I've fallen in love with him now for real, as he's dying, and...
我看着他 他就要死了 阿伦 他马上就
Uh, I look at him, and he's about to go, Alan. He's moments...
我照顾他直到结束 然后呢?
I took care of him through this, Alan. What now, then?
请听题
JlMMY: Let's listen.
你和七个孩子都好么?
Hello, Mary. How are you and the seven kids?
如你所听到的那样 为了波普的钱 我们当然会放了他
As you probably heard by now, we sure gave that Pope a run for his money.
- 米姆 - 应该是罗伯特・E・李
- JlMMY: Mim. - MlM: Um, that would be Robert E. Lee.
他的妻子是玛莉・帕克・卡斯蒂斯 我记得他有七个孩子
His wife was Mary Parke Custis. I know he had seven children.
他应该是在说波普 波普在马纳萨斯战役中被他打败了
Um, and he would be talking about Pope, who he defeated at the Battle of Manassas.
完全正确 米姆小姐 下一题
JlMMY: Absolutely right, Miss Mim. Next question.
加油 振作起来 伙计
Come on, come on, come on. Snap out of it, man.
加油 斯坦利
Come on. Stanley.
(法语对话)
Bonjour, Josephine. Maintenant je suis en Egypte.
是的 米姆
JlMMY: Yes, Mim.
应该是拿破仑和约瑟芬的对话
MlM: Um, that would be Napoleon speaking to Josephine.
完全正确 加 500分 下一题
JlMMY: Absolutely right, for 500. Next voice.
我不想他死 我原先不爱他
I don't want him to die. I didn't love him when we met...
我还背着他做了那么多坏事
...and I did so many bad things to him that he doesn't know.
我要和他坦白 我现在爱他
Things that I want to confess to him. But now I do. I love him.
- 琳达 你到底吃什么药了? - 别他妈老提什么嗑药了!
- Linda, what kind of medication are you on? - This isn't any fucking medication talking!
不是的 不是的 你能别把钱给我吗?你是律师 你可以的
Can you give me nothing? You have power of attorney.
你最后能把遗嘱改了么?
Can you go in the final fucking moments and change the will?
我一分钱也不要
l- I don't want any money.
不然我无法原谅自己的 我做太多坏事了
I couldn't live with myself with this thing that I've done.
我到处乱搞 我不停地骗他
I fucked around. I fucking cheated on him. I fucking cheated on him.
听着 听着 你是他的律师 我们的律师
There. There. You're his lawyer, our lawyer.
我是他妻子 我们结了婚 我背叛了他
I am his wife. We are married. I broke the contract of marriage.
我和别的男人上过无数次床 我帮他们口交
I fucked around on him many times. I sucked other men's cocks.
通奸并不违法
Adultery is not against the law.
法庭上用这个拒绝遗嘱是行不通的
lt's not something you can use in court to discredit the will.
- 琳达 冷静 - 我做不到
- Linda. Linda, calm down. - I can't.
你不一定要改遗嘱
You don't have to change the will.
如果你什么都不想继承 遗嘱生效时你可以声明的
lf you wanna take nothing, renounce the will when the time comes.
什么意思?那钱给谁?
What does that mean? Where does the money go?
- 继承给直系亲属 - 什么意思? 弗兰克?
- lt goes to the nearest relative. - What's that? Frank?
不 不能这样 厄尔什么都不想给他
No, no, no. That can't happen. EarI doesn't want him to have anything.
- 但只能这样 - 简直在放屁
- That's what will happen. - This is so fucked up.
琳达 别说了!
Linda, stop!
你先冷静冷静 好好想想
Now, you take a moment, you breathe...
- 把话好好说 - 闭上你的嘴
- ...and one thing at a time. - Shut the fuck up.
- 想要我帮你吗? - 闭上你的嘴!
- You want me to help you? - Shut the fuck up.
- 你需要清醒一下 - 你最好闭上你的臭嘴
- You need to sober up. - Now, you must really shut the fuck up.
求你了 快闭嘴
Now. Please, shut the fuck up.
- 琳达 - 我走了
- Linda. - I have to go.
- 我帮你叫车吧 - 闭嘴!
- Let me call you a car, Linda. - Shut the fuck up.
现在 想象你正参加一场即兴演奏会
JlMMY: Now, imagine that you are attending a jam session...
古典作曲家们
...of classical composers...
将共同谱曲组成这首古典的低吟
...and they have each done an arrangement of the classic favorite, Whispering.
现在 新世界口琴三人组
Now, we have here the New World Harmonica Trio...
将为我们演奏
...who are going to play, uh-
主题的三 三个变奏
Uh, three, um- Uh, variations on the theme...
就像 嗯
...as the, uh- As-
分别由三个作曲家做成
As three classical composers might have written it.
你们要说出第一个作曲家
So you are to name the, uh, first composer.
各位?
Guys?
- 是的 陶德 - 好吧 吉米 听起来像勃拉姆斯
- JlMMY: Yes, Todd. - Well, Jimmy, that sounded like Brahms.
有点像他的匈牙利舞曲第六号
Uh, a bit like his Hungarian Dance Number Six.
太棒了 陶德 下一个 请听
That is excellent, Todd. Next composer, guys.
斯坦利
Stanley the man.
我不知道答案
I don't know the answer.
不对
That is not right.
不是这个答案 斯坦利
That's not right, Stanley.
正确答案应该是拉威尔
The correct answer is Ravel.
拉威尔
Ravel.
下面我们将听到第三位作曲家
Uh, and now I'm gonna have our three whistlers, um...
请说出下一个音乐家
...please to present the next, uh, musical....
一共有三个音乐题
There were three, uh, musical sections here...
现在是第三题 这位作曲家
...and this will be the third section that the whistlers....
他们会演奏他的作品的一小段
Um, and they'll play a piece that's...
非常容易 其实答案是肖邦
lt's very recognizable. lt's Chopin, actually, and, uh....
好吧 出自马尔什风格
Well, it's taken- lt's in the style of Marche Militaire.
非常熟悉的一段旋律
lt's a very recognizable piece.
好吧 你们只要仔细地聆听
So if you please just listen to this...
我保证很容易说出答案
...and I'm sure you can identify the, uh....
我好像自己把答案说出来了先
I'm sort of giving away the answer here, but-
答案是肖邦 我不是故意要说出答案的
lt's Chopin. I don't mean to give away the answer.
只是 我只是
lt's just- Please, just-
请大家听演奏 肖邦的选段
Well, sing us a ditty, guys. A Chopin ditty.
让我们听一下肖邦的曲子现在 哦不
Let's have a Chopin ditty here. I can't....
- 切到片头 快切片头 - 切片头 快
- Go to the card. Go to the fucking card. - Go to the card. Go.
切到片头
Go to the card.
好 我回来了
Okay, I'm back.
除了杯子 这杯咖啡还是蛮不错的
JlM: For not a fresh cup, this is a good cup of coffee.
谢谢 想聊点什么?
CLAUDlA: Thank you. What do you wanna talk about?
不知道啊
I don't know.
- 你想聊么? - 是的 想
- Do you want to talk? - Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- 好吧 - 嗯
- Okay. - Um...
你叫什么?
What's your name?
吉姆・卡伦
Jim Kurring.
- 快打911 - 我想我是中风了
- Call 911. - I think I had a stroke.
不 不 不 没事儿 我还行
No, no, no. I'm fine. I'm all right.
- 把节目先录完吧 - 不 必须叫救护车来
- I wanna finish the show. - No, we need to call this quits.
- 别他妈动我! - 让他扶着你
- Get your hands off me. - Let this guy help you.
- 我给你说 是这样的 - 打 911 赶快去 玛莉
- Look, I just- I'll tell you what happened. - Call 911. Do it right now, Mary.
我跌倒了 一下子看不到了 不过没事了 放开我
I felI down and I couldn't see for a minute, but I'm okay. Get your hands off me.
- 你丫是不是尿裤子了?! - 闭嘴!
- Did you fucking piss your pants? - Shut up.
- 怎么了? - 没事! 走开!
- What happened? What's going on? - Nothing. Go away.
别和我这么说话
Don't tell me to go away.
我是负责人 你必须回答我的问题
I'm the coordinator for the show, and you will answer the questions I ask.
- 到底出什么事了? - 怎么回事?
- Now, what is going on? You- - What's the problem?
- 没事 我没事 - 为什么不回答那些问题?
- Nothing. I'm fine. - Why didn't you answer those questions?
- 我不会 - 胡扯!
- I didn't know the answer. - Bullshit! Bullshit!
你肯定会回答
You know the answer to every question.
我都知道答案 我没你一半聪明都
I knew the answers. I'm not half as smart as you...
到底出什么事了?
...so what the hell happened?
- 我不知道 - 他尿裤子了
- I don't know. - He pissed his pants.
你尿裤子了?
You pissed your pants?
- 没有 我没有 我没事儿! - 站起来
- No, I didn't. I'm fine. - Stand up.
- 我真的没事儿 - 站起来!
- I said I'm fine. I'm fine. - Stand up.
天哪 斯坦利 为什么这么做?
Oh, Jesus, Stanley, what the fuck did you do that for?
只是想继续比赛 继续下去 我没事儿
I just wanna keep playing. I'll keep playing. I'm fine.
非常好
That's great.
对于演员来说 这就是精神食粮
I mean, you know that, to a performer, that's food, right?
告诉他你们喜欢他 他会感激不尽的
That shows that you love him, and I'm sure he appreciates it.
一切正常 别紧张 夫人 一切正常
Everything's fine. Relax. Relax, darling. Everything's fine.
没事儿了
I'm okay.
好了 我没事儿了
All right, see? I'm all right.
真他妈傻逼 是吗 我?上帝啊
lt's pretty fucking stupid, isn't it? Jesus Christ.
他们怎么想啊?
What the fuck do they think out there?
他们肯定笑死了
They must be laughing their asses off.
就告诉他们我膝盖扭了什么的
Tell them I got a bad knee or some fucking thing.
真他妈有意思
Ha, ha. This is fucking funny.
- 现在怎么办? - 就这么办
- What do you guys wanna do? - Just what I said.
- 还能继续下去么? - 能
- Are we going to continue with this game? - Yes.
好吧! 听我说!
All right, you look at me. Look at me.
你离纪录就差两天了
You are two days away from this record. Okay? Nobody's ever done that.
从来没有人能做到的 你坚持下来的话 我什么都答应你!
You get through this, I'll get you anything you want. Anything.
- 只要能坚持下来 好么? - 好
- You just gotta get through this, okay? - Okay.
好吧 坐好了 孩子!对不起把你胳膊弄疼了
Hang in there, buddy. I'm sorry I squeezed your arm.
喂 我爱你
Hey. I love you.
- 还要继续么? - 真他妈的
- Are we doing this? - Fucking stupidity.
- 当初怎么没找个医生来? - 别逼他了
- Why don't I put the medic on? - Don't let him do this.
- 他已经做了30年了 - 你不知道
- He's been doing it for 30 years. - You don't know.
这只是场游戏 玛莉
lt's a fucking game show, Mary.
听见没?
Hear that?
- 哦 疼吗? - 不疼
- JlM: Ah, yeah. Does that hurt? - No.
- 怎么弄的? - 从耳朵里
- What is it? - lt's in my ear.
叫做...TMJ
lt's, um, TMJ.
好像正式的就是这么叫的
lt's what it's called. Technically.
为什么不就叫个卡下巴什么的?
How about they just call it, you know, clicking jaw?
- 是啊 磕下巴也行 - 是啊 也不错啊?
- Pain in the jaw, yeah. Ha, ha. - Yeah. How about that?
- 很好记 - 对啊 我
- Be easier to remember. - Yeah. lt gets....
我一直不知道我会做这个 呵呵
l- I don't even know if I have it, actually.
15- L- 27 伸出头来
WOMAN：15- L- 27 15- L- 27 head out to
很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我是库德・赛文
15- L- 27, I'm currently code seven.
不好意思 有工作
I'm sorry. This is my job.
15- L- 27 收到
L- 27, roger.
威廉姆- 35 如果威廉姆- 38提到我你能看到吗?
William- 35, can you see if you can raise 10- William- 28 for me?
收到 看不到 这只能传递信息
Roger. Disregard. lt was just the information passed on.
我们才刚刚开始聊啊
You were just getting warmed up. Getting started.
是啊 我得走了
Yeah. I gotta go.
嗯 要是下次还能看见你的小把戏 或者你再把音量调太大声的话
Well, if this joker shows up again, or you got your music up too loud...
我们或许还能再一起喝杯咖啡啦
...maybe we can have another cup of coffee.
如果你不是因为187来这里的话
lf you're not here for a 187.
- 不 不要这么说 - 好吧
- No. Do not joke about that, okay? - Okay.
- 我已经受够了 - 对不起
- I seen too many of those. - I'm sorry.
没事儿 你不是有意的 没事
No. it's all right. You were kidding. lt's okay.
好吧
All right.
继续练习你的下巴 还有音乐小声些 好么?
Well, you keep your chin up and your music down, okay?
好的 很高兴认识你 吉姆警官
Yes, I will. lt was nice to meet you, Officer Jim.
- 叫吉姆就好 - 嗯 好的
- Just Jim. - Yeah. Good. Okay.
- 好的 再见克劳迪娅 - 再见
- Okay. Bye- bye, Claudia. - Bye.
- 怎么啦?忘了什么东西是么? - 不 我
- What is it? Did you forget something? - No. No, I'm...
我一直想
I was- I was wondering....
哦!我觉得自己好傻
Man, I feel like a bit of a scumbucket doing this...
我来这里是执行任务的
...since I came here as an officer of the law...
但我会恨死自己 如果我不把真话说出来的话
...but I feel like I'd be a fool if I didn't do something I really wanna do...
- 我想和你约会 - 你想和我约会?
- ...which is to ask you for a date. - You wanna go on a date with me?
- 是的 想 - 嗯
- Please, yes. - Ahem.
- 这样不对是吧? - 有点
- Well, is that illegal? - Sort of.
那么那我愿意! 咱们去哪里?
Then I'd like to go. What do you wanna do?
不知道 还没想过 骗你的 我其实一直在想
I don't know. I hadn't thought about it. That's not true. I have thought about it.
打从你开门时我就在想了
I've been thinking since you opened the door.
- 真的? - 是
- Really? - Yeah.
我刚以为你只是逗我玩呢
I thought you were flirting with me.
就今晚怎么样?
You want to go tonight?
我没事 可以的
I'm- No- I'm off tonight, yeah. That would be-
- 几点? - 8点
- What time? - 8 o'clock.
- 我10点才能下班 - 那10点
- I don't get off until 10:00. - 10 o'clock.
- 好的 - 好
- Okay. - Yeah.
- 很好 - 好 再见
- Yeah. Fine. - Yeah. Bye.
弗兰克 我真的不是想要为难你
GWENOVlER: Frank, I'm really not trying to attack you here.
只是觉得是否需要弄清一些事情 关于你的
I think that if you have something that needs to be cleared up, well, then...
我刚说了你的父亲叫厄尔・帕特里奇
I was told that your father is Earl Partridge.
我听说他离开了你和你母亲
I was told that he left you and your mother...
你一直照顾着生病的母亲
...and you were forced to take care of your mother during her illness...
是你照料了患癌症的她
...that you took care of your mother while she struggled with cancer...
然后西姆斯小姐成为你的监护人
...and that Miss Simms became your caretaker...
自从你母亲去世后
...when your mother finally passed away.
能谈谈你母亲么 弗兰克
Can you talk about your mother, Frank?
不 不 不是这样 知道么!即使你不愿意帮她口交
No, not true. You know what? Even if you don't get to pump her...
你也应该尽量表现得非常尊重女性
...you still need to start honing your skills on a feminist.
- 你必须这样做 - 我会的
- You need to do that. - I will.
- 我是唐尼 - 我是珍妮特
- This is Doc. Doc, it's Janet.
- 什么事?珍妮特 - 我得和弗兰克通话 他在吗?
- What's up, Janet? - I have to talk to Frank. ls he nearby?
- 他正接受采访呢 珍妮特 - 叫他出来
- Uh, he's in the interview, Janet. - lnterrupt him.
- 让他立刻来接电话 - 怎么了?
- Get him on the phone with me right away. - What happened?
唐尼 赶快叫弗兰克来接电话
Doc, go get Frank and put him on the phone.
哦 别这样 弗兰克
GWENOVlER: Oh, come on, Frank.
你怎么了?
What are you doing?
我怎么了?
What am I doing?
是啊
Yeah.
我在默默地审判你
I'm quietly judging you.
五 四 三 二
And five, four, three, two....
哦?
Yeah?
哦 重新回到现场
Oh, boy, what a day. What a round.
重新和我一起进入
Back and in for me...
最后的一对一单元 看看谁会想到最后
...and the final one- on- one round to determine who's who today.
首先我们来看看两队积分板
Let's check the scores on the board, shall we?
嗯 少年组刚好2000
Well, the kids have an even 2000...
成年组则超过4700
...and the adults are way up with 47.
不过 这并不意味着 孩子们不可能反败为胜
Now, that doesn't mean that this game is out of reach for the kids.
- 队长 你们选出谁参加了么? - 就是我啦 吉米
- Elders, who's the lucky so- and- so? - lt's gonna be me, Jimmy.
请上台来 米姆
Come on over, Mim.
我不要去 这次我不行了
I don't wanna go. I can't do it this time.
你他妈的说什么呢?
What the fuck are you talking about?
你必须去啊 斯坦利 你是最聪明的
You have to go, Stanley. You're the smartest.
我不要去 你们随便谁上去不行么?
I don't wanna go. Why can't one of you do it?
你要敢不起来上台去 我就踹死你
RlCHARD: lf you don't fucking stand up and get over there, I'm gonna beat your ass.
我受够了总做第一 不得不做这做那
I'm sick of being the one who always has to do everything.
- 我不要老是这样! - 孩子们 我想不用问了吧
- I don't wanna be the one always. - JlMMY: Kids, I don't even have to ask.
快过来
Stanley, get your butt over here.
我要疯了
I'm sick.
我不行了
I'm sick here now.
我经常这样郁闷得死去活来
I confuse melancholy with depression sometimes.
- 嗯嗯 - 你瞧
- Mm- hm. - You see?
为什么不快回去呢 朋友?你的甜点要凉了
Why don't you run along now, friend? Your dessert is getting cold.
- 我要疯了 - 挺好的
- I'm sick. - Stay that way.
我是疯了 我恋爱了
I'm sick, and I'm in love.
你看上去好像为情所困似的
You seem the sort of person who confuses the two.
完全正确!
That's right.
你从来没有这么正确过
That's the first time you've been right.
我为情所困 但是我不怕!
I confuse the two, and I don't care.
嘿 喂
Hey. Hey!
我爱你
I love you.
我爱你 我疯了
I love you, and I'm sick.
咱们明天再见面
I'll talk to you- I'll talk to you tomorrow.
明天我要做口腔手术 牙齿矫正
I'm getting corrective oral surgery tomorrow, for my teeth.
我爱你 布拉德 我的好招待
I love you, Brad. Brad the bartender.
如果你也爱我的话 我会好好待你的
lf you wanna love me back, I'll be good to you.
我会对你好得不能再好的
I'll be goddamn good for you.
我不会因为你这个不懂那个不懂而生气
I won't be mad if you don't know who said what.
我不会因为你回答错误而惩罚你
I won't punish you if you get the answer wrong.
- 布拉德 亲爱的 - 我可以教你 告诉你
- Brad, honey. - I can teach and tell you...
你的心智缺陷很严重
You have a special secret crush over there, I think.
别这么爱他 他会伤害得很惨的
Don't treat him too lovely. He might get hurt.
- 给我闭嘴!你别管闲事! - 小心点 小子
- You shut up! Mind your own business. - Gently, son.
我知道你现在并不爱我
I know you don't love me now.
错把可爱当恋爱是非常危险的
lt's a dangerous thing to confuse children with angels.
知道共有的元素是什么吗?
Wanna know the common element for the entire group, like he asked?
我来告诉你们 我知道
I'll tell you the answer, because I had that one.
我会回答这个问题
I had that question.
碳 是碳
Uh, carbon. Carbon.
在铅笔芯中 它是以石墨形式存在的
ln pencil lead, it's in the form of graphite...
在煤矿中 它和各种杂质混杂在一起
...in coal, it's mixed up with other impurities...
而在钻石中 它以最坚固的形式存在
...and in the diamond, it's in hard form.
好吧 我们只是需要元素的名字就好
Well, all we really wanted to know was the common element, Donnie...
谢谢你告诉我们这么多不必要的知识
...but thank you for all that unnecessary knowledge. Ha, ha.
这些孩子 脑子里净是这些毫无用处的东西
Kids. Heads so full of useless knowledge.
谢谢 谢谢
Thank you. Thank you.
书上如是说 虽然时过境迁
The book says, We may be through with the past...
但我们不会改变!
...but the past is not through with us.
还有
And....
不对 那一点也不危险 误把可爱当恋爱
No, it is not dangerous to confuse children with angels.
是 好的
Yeah. Okay.
嗯 终于等到这一天了
Well, that is what I wait for.
我等着别人回电 等待着祈祷着
I wait for those calls. And I wait and I pray.
突然上帝说
And sometimes Jesus says:
吉姆 今天要给你个惊喜
Jim, I got a surprise for you today.
我要让你见这个小姑娘 行吗?
I want you to meet this young lady, okay?
然后 然后该怎么办就看你的啦
Now, where it goes from there is up to you.
相信你不会搞砸的啦
And I don't think you're gonna screw it up, okay?
那么 上帝啊 我现在要回答你
And, God, I'm telling you right now...
我不会把它搞砸的!您把这个机会赐给我
... I will not screw it up. You gave me an opportunity.
我会好好对这位姑娘的
I'm gonna treat this young lady right.
我是个快乐的警察
I'm a happy cop.
这个人违反交规 慢着!
Yeah. lt's called jaywalking. Slow down.
我想让给别人 吉米
Uh, I'm gonna pass, Jimmy.
斯坦利 那让别的孩子上来吧
JlMMY: Stanley, passing to one of the other kids.
我们都决定让斯坦利上去 吉米
We want Stanley to go, Jimmy.
我不要去
I don't wanna go.
- 我正在往电梯走 珍妮特 - 好 菲尔 在听吗?
- Walking towards the elevator, Janet. - Fine. Phil, are you still there?
对 在呢 我想问你一句
PHlL: Yeah, I'm here. I wanna ask you one question.
菲尔 你和其他任何人说过此事吗?
Phil, have you talked to anyone else about this?
- 不 没有 - 好 那咱们都别说出去
- PHlL: No, I haven't. - Good, let's keep it that way, okay?
为了安全 为了一切 你能了解么?
All the security and whatnot. You understand?
弗兰克和家庭的关系正处在非常脆弱的时刻
This could be a delicate situation for the family.
到底出什么事了?闭嘴 唐尼
What's going on? What's happening? Doc, fuck off.
菲尔 再等片刻
Phil, hang in just one more minute, okay?
- 马上就好了 - 谢谢
- I'm gonna put you on hold. - PHlL: Thank you.
快到了没 唐尼?
How close are you, Doc?
理查德?茱莉亚
Richard? Julia?
孩子们 怎么回事?
Kids, what's going on?
我需要一个做一对一的选手
I need a player here for one- on- one.
我们选 斯坦利上 吉米 可我们不知道他为什么不去
RlCHARD: We want Stanley to go, Jimmy, and we're not sure why he won't.
总是我来回答问题 我一点儿都不想做了
I always go. I always answer the questions, and I don't wanna do it anymore.
他怎么回事儿啊? 出什么毛病了?
What the fuck is he doing? What's wrong with him?
我不知道
I have no idea.
- 我走出电梯了 珍妮特 - 好 好样的
- I'm getting off the elevator, Janet. - Good. Good boy.
我穿过走廊
I'm walking down the hall.
这孩子还没起来 录不下去了
This fucking kid ain't getting up, and we don't have a show.
这是现场直播啊 大家!
Live television, ladies and germs. Heh.
小混蛋
Little prick.
- 这算什么啊 当游戏玩啊? - 他到底在干什么?
- What is this, a point? A game? - What the hell is he doing?
快起来啊 孩子 快点
Come on. Get the fuck up, kid, come on.
时间到
Time's up.
你这算什么? 干坐着耗掉吗?
So that's what you did? You sat it out?
你要我抽时间 我给你时间了
You wanted my time. I gave it to you.
你把我称作骗子 你以此指控我
You called me a liar. You made accusations.
还什么 好吧 我要是真清楚一切的话
You said:
那我还问你做什么
Well, if I had known, then I wouldn't have asked.
好吧 这不是个人攻击
So it's not an attack.
我也不想成为 什么不守信用的人
See, I don't wanna be the sort of fella who doesn't keep his word...
所以我给你他妈的时间!贱人
...so I gave you my fucking time, bitch.
- 操 - 啊
- Now fuck- - Unh!
是该死的珍妮特的 手机上的出了些情况
lt's fucking Janet. There's a situation on the phone.
为了现在 你可以买《诱惑与征服》
FRANK: If you order now, you can get Seduce and Destroy...
加上录像带和录音带和优惠券
...plus videos and audio cassettes, and a coupon...
为了弗兰克T・J・麦吉的未来研讨会
...for Frank T.J. Mackey's next seminar.
孩子正在思想斗争 观众朋友们
The indecision of a child, ladies and germs.
一点都不好笑
This isn't funny.
一点都不可爱
This isn't cute.
不是么 我们这样?
See, the way we're looked at....
我不是玩具
Because I'm not a toy.
我不是玩偶
I'm not a doll.
仅仅是因为你想让我们看起来天真可爱 不是么?
The way we're looked at because you think we're cute.
是因为什么?
Because what?
我这么做就会让你们觉得很怪异么?
What? I'm made to feel like a freak...
要是我回答问题呢
...if I answer questions...
要是我聪明
...or I'm smart...
要是我一定要去厕所呢?
...or I have to go to the bathroom?
你说呢 吉米?
What is that, Jimmy?
说话啊?
What is that?
我在问你呢
I'm asking- I'm asking you that.
我不知道 斯坦利
I'm not sure, Stanley.
15- L- 27 请求支援
JlM: 15- L- 27, uh, I need some help.
这里发生枪击
We have shots fired.
答案是 哈姆雷特给克劳迪亚斯
DONNlE: lt's Hamlet to Claudius.
父亲的邪恶继承给了孩子 出自《威尼斯商人》
The sins of the father laid upon the children is Merchant of Venice.
但原出处是《旧约》25章
Borrowed from Exodus 25.
对不起 弗兰克 我实在不知道还应该做什么
I'm sorry. I didn't know what else you wanted me to do here.
我刚才把该问的都向他问了
There was nothing- I asked him all the right questions.
他是你父亲的看护人员 正和他在一起
He's his nurse. He's sitting there with him.
- 我刚才能听见你父亲的声音 - 慢着 他在他们家里是么?
- I heard your father in the background. - Wait. He's there at their house?
他们就在他家里 我问他详细地址 他告诉我了
They're at the house. I asked him the exact address, and he gave it, Frank.
我知道你很难受现在
I know this is really hard for you right now.
你想说什么的话 就告诉我具体信息的吧
No. You gotta give me things, Janet. Give me things.
我要实在点的信息 这才是我需要的
Give me information. I want the information. That's what I want.
- 那就是具体信息 弗兰克 - 他说了些什么?
- That's the information, Frank. - What did he say?
我根本不在乎他是谁 他想怎么样?
I am not gonna take care of him. What does he want? Did he say?
弗兰克 你到底想让我怎么样?
Frank, what the fuck do you want me to do?
- 听着 - 我想你这样 珍妮特
- Listen. - What I want you to do, Janet...
他妈的做好你的工作!
...is I want you to do your fucking job!
他妈的我完成了我的工作!
I am doing my fucking job, Frank.
让你拿起电话
You fucking get on the phone.
我不是玩偶! 我不是傻兮兮的小可爱!
I'm not a doll. I'm not silly and cute.
就因为我聪明 我就得
I'm smart. That should make me something...
就得供你们观赏 这孩子多么笨拙可爱!
...so people can watch how silly it is that he's smart!
我知道 我都知道
I know. I know things.
我知道 我知道
I know- I know...
我知道我得去厕所了 我请求过你们
I know I have to go to the bathroom, and....
停止直播 切到片尾
Take us off the air. Go to the credits.
- 打职员表 - 够了
- Roll the credits. - Enough.
操他妈的! 狗日的!
God fucking damn it! Son of a bitch!
这是怎么了?! 操! 操! 操!
What the fuck? Fuck! Fuck! Fuck!
斯坦利 别这么对我!
Stanley, don't do this to me!
我得把枪找着
Gotta find the gun.
在哪儿呢 到底?
Where is it, now?
哪儿去了?!
Where is it?
好 开始吧
All right. All right, let's go.
哪儿去了? 好好找
Where is it? Find it.
找到它!
Find it.
找到枪啊 吉姆
Find the gun, Jim!
你还要我说什么?
What more do you want me to say? - Just give me a second.
赶快决定啊
You need to make a decision.
- 你为什么不 ? - 好了 让我想想
- Look, why don't you- ? - Look, just give me a second.
- 让我先想想 - 嗯嗯
- Give me a second. - Uh- huh.
弗兰克
Frank?
想什么想 弗兰克?
What the fuck, Frank?
你要我怎么办现在?
What do you want me to do?
我再说一遍 现在订购《诱惑与征服》
FRANK I'm gonna say again. Order Seduce and Destroy now...
我保证 我保证会退款
...and I guarantee, I guarantee, money- back-
琳达
PHlL: Linda.
- 你在做什么? - 我找到弗兰克了 厄尔的儿子
- What are you doing? - I got Frank. Frank, EarI's son.
- 把它挂掉! - 别 他刚让我
- Hang up. - No, he asked me to get him.
快给我挂掉!
LlNDA: Put the fucking phone down!
- 放下电话! - 不!
- Hang it up! Hang it up! - I can't! I can't!
弗兰克 在听吗?
Frank, are you there?
我想让你和他谈谈
I want you to talk to him.
弗兰克
Frank?
我要把他接进来了
I'm gonna put him on.
放下电话! 不许你这么做!
Hang it up! You don't do that.
不许打给她 你什么都不该知道
You don't call him. You don't know.
别卷进他的家庭 我的家庭里来!
To get involved in this business of his. Of his- Of my family.
我们的家庭 我和他 懂吗?
This is the family. Me and him. Understand?
- 没别人了! 没有了! - 我只是
- There's no one else. No one else! - I was just-
那个人 那个漂亮的人
That man. That beautiful man....
他儿子早就没了 他死了
His son does not exist. He's dead. He's dead.
谁让你这么做的?
Who asked you to do that?
- 厄尔让的 - 胡说!
- Earl did. - Bullshit!
- 是他 很抱歉 真的是他 - 胡说! 他才不会这么做呢!
- He did. Please, I'm sorry, he did. - Bullshit! He didn't ask you!
他根本就不想见他 不想和他说话!
He doesn't wanna talk to him, so fuck you that he asked that!
这个家庭只有我和他! 没别人了!
There's no one but me and him! No one!
对不起 他 他让我做的
I'm sorry. l... He just.... He asked me.
对不起 对不起
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
玛莉 带我离开这里 我得回家了 见露丝
Mary, take me out of here. I got to go home to Rose.
- 靠着我 - 玛莉 送他回家
- Just lean on me. - Mary, take him home.
- 快! 回后台吧 - 我们到底赢没赢啊?
- ln the back. - Did we win or lose?
我也不知道 我们需要谈一下
I don't know. We gotta talk.
你们输了 在时间到后就要算分数了
You lost. They go to the score the time they called it.
根本没有什么规则
JULlA: That's not an official rule. - Not an official rule?
- 根本没有什么规则? - 胡扯
- That's an official rule, baby. - That's bullshit!
你听谁说的? 从那本书看来的?不一样的!!这是场游戏表演!
Who says that? ln what rule book? This is different! lt's a game show!
- 跟你的狗屁规则一点关系没有! 理查德 闭嘴 别说了!
- They don't go by fucking sports rules! - Richard, shut it and cut it out.
要是他不尿裤子 我们早赢那些废物们了!
lf he hadn't pissed his pants, we would have won this motherfucker!
早赢了 你把我宝贝儿子怎么着了 伯特?
What did you do with my goddamn kid, Burt?
别他妈拽我 你这个废物
Stanley! Get your fucking hands off me, you boy- producer punk. Hey, Stanley!
哦天哪 为什么是我?
Oh, Lord, why is this happening to me?
上帝啊 快帮我找出来吧
God, please help me figure it out.
我会玩完的
I'm lost out here.
到底为什么偏偏是我啊 老天!
I don't understand why it's happening, God.
别这样 老天
Please, God.
不管我做错了什么 我都会改正的 我会认认真真做对的
Whatever it is I did, I'm gonna fix it. I'm gonna do the right thing.
好吧 老天求求你了 让我找到枪吧
Please, God, help me find the gun.
嗯
Uh....
我爱你
I love you.
听我说 菲尔
Uh, listen, Phil.
嗯
Um...
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
对不起 我刚才扇了你
I'm sorry I slapped your face.
好吗?我
Okay? l, um...
我晕了刚才
I don't know what I'm doing.
我不知道怎么会这样
I don't know how to do this.
做什么我都能搞砸
I do things, and I fuck up.
我搞砸了
I fucked up.
能原谅我吗?
Can you forgive me?
没关系的
Yeah. lt's all right.
能告诉他吗 我对不起他
Can you tell him I'm sorry...
所有做过的事情 我搞砸的事情
...for the things that I've done, that I fucked up?
对不起
I'm sorry. Um....
我要出去了 离开这里
I'm going to turn and walk away and not look at him...
不再见他 不再看他 我的厄尔 还有告诉他
...and not see my man, my Earl, and tell him, uh....
一切都好 我很好
Tell him, lt's okay. I'm okay.
告诉他 谢谢你的照顾
Tell him, Thank you for taking care....
我现在一切都很好
Whole thing is okay with me.
一切都好
And I know.
欢迎你们回来!
Welcome back from the break.
- 喜欢那些玉米片吗 你们? - 喜欢
- How did you guys like those nachos? - AUDlENCE: Yeah.
你们来这里不是为了什么狗屁玉米片的
Yeah. Oh, yeah. Well, you are not here for the fucking food.
你们来这里是来接受我的开导 我的启发
You are here for me to enlighten you, to edify you...
把你们送向现在看来并不遥远的未来
...to send you off into the now- not- so- unknown future...
好吧 跟着我继续
...so come along with me.
如何伪装得友善和同情
How to fake like you are nice and caring.
哦 我不需要麦克风
No, I don't want a microphone.
注意 这个
Now, this....
这个 是很重要的一章 你将会看到
Ahem, this is quite an important chapter, as you will see.
但让我们先来个基本事实 让我们现在开始 伙计们
But let's get down to brass tacks. Let's get right down to it, boys.
- 男人是废物 - 什么?
- Men are shit. - AUDlENCE: What?
什么? 男人是废物
What? Men are shit.
她们不这样说吗?
Well, isn't that what they say?
因为我们就会做坏事 不是吗?我们老做一些可怕的 讨厌的 糟糕的事情
Because we do bad things, don't we? We do horrible, heinous, terrible things.
一些女人们决不会做的事情
Things that no woman would ever do.
不 女士们从不撒谎的
No, women, they don't lie.
不 女士们从不欺骗的
No, women don't cheat.
女士们从不操纵我们
Women don't manipulate us.
但是看看真正的情景吧
But you see what I'm getting at. Oh, yeah, you see what I'm getting at.
生活中是这样的 可怜的小男孩
You see what society does? Boy. Little boys, it's:
哦 女人啊!
Wow. Woman.
- 我们必须懂得道歉 对不起 - 算了
- We are taught to apologize. I am sorry. - Give it up.
对不起 宝贝儿 真的对不起
I am so sorry, baby. I am so sorry.
到底是什么
What is it that- ?
我们到底需要什么?
What is it, huh, that we need?
是她们的肉体么?她们的爱?
ls it their pussies? Their, uh, love?
妈妈不让我去踢球
Mommy wouldn't let me play soccer...
爸爸 打了我 这就是我
...and Daddy, oh, he hit me, so that's who I am.
因此我才会成为现在的我?
That's why I do what I do? Heh.
- 混蛋 - 对
- Fucking bullshit. - That's right.
- 我对得起自己 我就是我 - 很对
- I will not apologize for who I am. - Right on.
- 我想做什么是我自己的事! - 是
- I will not apologize for what I need. - Yeah.
我想要什么是我自己的事!
- I will not apologize for what I want! AUDlENCE: Yeah!
现在拿出你们的蓝色小册子
Okay. Go to your blue booklets right now.
我要你们翻到18页
I want you to turn to page 18 in your blue booklets.
真他妈操蛋!
Fuck. This is fucking bullshit!
我要你们拿出白色手册
I want you to go to your white- Your white books.
是白色那本才对
That's what I want you to go to.
翻到白册子的23页
Go to 23 in your white books.
如何伪装得让你看起来友善和富同情心
How to fake like you are a nice and caring person.
菲尔 菲尔
Phil. Phil.
喂 过来 过来
Hey, come here. Come here.
嗯
Uh...
菲尔
...Phil...
我
... I'm....
- 我要说说话 - 好的
- I'm gonna try talk. - Okay.
听着 我要和你
And I'm trying to....
- 说些什么 东西 - 好
- To say something. - Okay.
你认识莉莉么 菲尔? 知道她么?
Do you know Lily, Phil? Do you know her?
不认识
No.
- 莉莉 - 不 不认识
- Lily? - No, I don't.
哦
Oh.
她是我的爱人 我的生命 一切
She's my love, my life, love of it. Yeah.
上学的时候
ln school....
我那时12岁 在六年级
I'm 12 years old, in school, in sixth grade.
我看见了她
I saw her.
我和她不在一间学校 不过
Yeah. I didn't go to that school, but....
反正我们见面了
But, uh, we met.
我朋友认识她
Uh, my friend knew her.
我就问
I said, uh:
这女孩是谁? 莉莉 怎么样?
What's that girl? How's that Lily?
哦 她很坏 她和好多人上过床
Oh, she's bad. She sleeps with guys.
没错 就是这么说的 然后有一天
Yeah, he said this, but then, sometimes....
我们本来不在一起上学 对吧
And I went to another school, you see.
但到了
Uh, but then, uh....
高中最后是什么来着 叫什么?
When high school at an end, what's that?
- 高中结束时候怎么说来着? - 毕业
- What is that, uh, when it gets to the end? - Graduation.
- 不是 不是 年级 是多少年级来着? - 12年级
- No, no, the grade. What grade are you in? - That's 12th.
哦 对对
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
嗯 我就是那时转到她学校的
Yeah. So I went to her school for that grade.
就是12年级
That's grade 12.
我们见面
And we meet.
她
She was...
漂亮死了
...fucking like a doll.
对 像个瓷娃娃
Yeah. A beautiful porcelain doll.
那小屁股
And the hips.
刚微微翘起来那种 见过么?
The child- bearing hips, you know that?
太漂亮了
So beautiful.
然后我就骗她
And I cheated on her...
一次次骗她
...over and over and over again...
因为我觉得这才是男人
...because I wanted to be a man...
我不想让她长大
...and I didn't want her to be a woman.
成为一个聪明 自由的人
You know, a smart, free person...
一个有主见的人
...who was something.
我很不喜欢那样
My fucking mind then.
太傻了我当时太傻了
So stupid, that fucking mind. Stupid.
上帝啊!
Jesus Christ.
我怎么会那样?当时怎么会那样想呢?
What would I think? Did I think for what I'd done?
她是我23年的妻子
She was my wife for 23 years
我却一次次地背叛她
...and I went behind her over and over.
我这个傻逼 天天跑出去 干别的女人
Fucking asshole that I am, I'd go out and I'd fuck...
然后回家 然后躺到她身边
...and I'd come home and get in her bed...
然后对她说 我爱你
...and say, I love you.
她是杰克的妈妈
This is Jack's mother.
他的母亲 莉莉
His mother, Lily.
他们两个
These two...
是我的
...that I had...
我却放弃了
...and I lost.
这就是我的忏悔
This is the regret that you make.
这就是
This is the...
我最后悔的 我所经受的
...regret that you make and the something you take...
这些事儿
...and the blah, blah, blah...
这些事儿 这些事儿
Something, something.
- 给我根烟 - 好
- Give me a cigarette. - Okay.
嗯
Uh....
像这样的错
Mistakes like this...
千万别犯
...you don't make.
可能以后
Sometimes...
你会做得挺对
...you make some, and okay.
有时候会做得不对 有时候
Not okay, sometimes, you make other ones.
是
Yeah.
然后记住应该更努力些
Know that you should do better.
我爱莉莉
I loved Lily.
我骗了她
I cheated on her.
她和我结婚23年
She was my wife for 23 years.
然后我有了个儿子
And I have a son.
然后她得了癌症
And she has cancer.
然后我离开了他们
And I'm not there...
然后他不得不自己照顾母亲
...and he's forced to take care of her.
他才14岁
He's 14 years old.
就得
To....
就得照顾自己的母亲 然后
To take care of his mother and....
然后看着她在自己面前死去
And watch her die on him.
这么小的孩子 而我却跑了
A little kid, and I'm not there.
然后她就死了
And she does die.
我那么爱她
I loved her so.
但她知道我都做了什么
And she knew what I did.
她知道我做得一切傻事
She knew all the fucking stupid things I'd done.
但是爱
But the love...
要比你能想象到的有力得多
...was stronger than anything you can think of.
我的忏悔!
The goddamn regret.
The goddamn regret!
现在我也要死了
And I'll die.
我要死了 我告诉你
Now I'll die, and I'll tell you what.
我一生最大的悔恨
The biggest regret of my life...
就是抛弃了我的真爱
I let my love go.
我做了什么?
What did I do?
我活了65岁
I'm 65 years old.
我羞愧万分
And I'm ashamed.
千万年前
Million years ago...
什么忏悔 什么罪恶
The fucking regret and guilt, these things...
统统都不存在
Don't ever let anyone ever say to you...
根本没有什么忏悔
...you shouldn't regret anything.
别这么做
Don't do that. Don't. Oh.
为自己所思所想而忏悔
You regret what you fucking want. Ah.
就这样 就这么做
Use that. Use that.
做什么事都应该忏悔 任何事
Use that regret for anything, any way you want.
你可以的 好吗?
You can use it, okay?
哦 上帝
Oh, God.
这一路上走得平平坦坦
This is a long way to go with no punch.
一个挺启发的
A little moral...
小故事 我说
...story, I say. Ha, ha.
爱情
Love.
这个破烂人生
This fucking life...
哦
Oh...
真他妈太长了
lt's so fucking hard.
太长了
So long.
人生根本不短 太长了
Life ain't short. lt's long.
真他妈的长
lt's long, God damn it.
妈的
Goddamn.
我做了些什么?
What did I do?
我做了些什么?我做了些什么?
What did I do? What did I do?
菲尔 菲尔 救救我
Phil. Phil, help me.
做了些什么?
What did I do?
- 嘿 怎么样? - 你感觉怎么样?
- Hey, Juan, how you doing? - How you feeling?
感觉如何?我想我还是在呆一会儿 坚持到结束了
Yeah, I think I'm going to stay on, stick it out.
- 你决定了? - 是的
- Are you sure? - Yeah.
- 好 - 行 晚安
- Okay. - All right, good night.
你真傻
You're so stupid.
你行的
You know, you know, you know.
开始吧
Go, go, go.
- 哦 丹尼尔 - 喂 亲爱的 我要你帮个忙
- Donnie. Oh, Donnie. - Hello, dear. I need a favor.
好的 好
PHlL: Okay, okay.
行了 一边去 迈克斯
Shh. All right, all right. Back up, back up. Back up, Max.
一边去 米勒斯
Back up, Miles. Back up.
- 你好 你是弗兰克? - 杰克对吧?
- Hello. You Frank? Jack, right? - Hello. How are you?
- 你就是菲尔? - 我是菲尔
- Are you Phil? - PHlL: Phil, yeah.
刚一直在等你接电话 后来吊线了
We, uh, tried to get in touch. We got disconnected.
边上去 迈克斯 嘿 快! 快点!
Stay in, Max. Stay in. Hey, hey, come on.
你还好吗?
All right? Please.
- 我收到消息了 - 一直找不到你
I got the message. - Yeah, I couldn't find you.
厄尔请求我 我就去找地址簿了 里面没有你电话 什么都没有
I looked through the address books. There's no number. There's nothing.
- 嘘 嘿 - 那个谁
- - Shh. Hey! - ls, uh, what's- her- name...?
琳达?哦不 她出去了 她不在这里
PHlL: Linda? No, she went out. She's not here.
嘿 真不好意思
Hey, I'm sorry, uh....
我不知道该做什么
You know, I don't know what to do here.
你爸爸叫我找到你 我连号码都没有
Um, your dad asked me to get in touch with you, and I didn't have the number.
就拨了那个号码 要进来吗?
You know, I called the number. Do you wanna come in?
- 好 嘿 菲尔 - 怎么了?
- Yeah. Hey, Phil? - Okay. Yeah?
别让狗离我太近 不然我就踢它们
I will drop- kick those fucking dogs if they come near me.
- 好吧 - 行?
- PHlL: All right. - Okay?
进来吧 这只叫布莱克
Come on in. Come on in. This is Blake.
- 这是米勒斯 - 都撵走
- This is Miles. - Clear them out.
都过来
PHlL: Here we go.
好了 他就在里面
All right, he's in here...
一起进去吧
...so we all go in here. Come on.
进来吧?
Wanna go in?
- 不 我先站一会 菲尔 - 好吧
- No, I just- Stand here a second, Phil. - Okay.
- 行吗? - 好吧
- Okay? - All right.
夫人!
Lady.
嘿 夫人
Hey, lady.
夫人 夫人
Lady. Lady.
嘿 醒一醒
Hey, wake up.
夫人
Lady.
你怎么啦?
What's wrong with you?
我们现在怎么办?
How do we do this, then?
就这么办吧
Well, we just do it.
继续下去 慢慢会好的
We do it. We figure it out.
就这么办吧
We do as we do, I guess.
你爱我么 露丝?
Do you love me, Rose?
你是我的男人
You are my handsome man.
我是个坏男人
- I'm a bad person. - Ha, ha, no. No.
我是说
I mean...
我得跟你说出来
... I'm telling you this now, you see....
因为我想一切都明明白白
You see, because I want everything to be clear and clean...
而且我要为我以前的所作所为道歉
...and I want to apologize for me and all the stupid things that I've done.
我骗过你
I've cheated on you.
我做过对不起你的事 我 非常难受
I've cheated on you, and it kills me...
一直悔恨不已
...and the guilt of what I've done....
我不想让你觉得
I don't want you to think-
你可能知道
Maybe you knew.
我想你早就知道了吧
I think maybe you've known.
那么我想说出来 不仅令我
So I hope this is not just for me....
能好过一些
For me to make myself feel better about what I've done...
而且我也不想令你觉得 自己和傻子一样
...but for you not to feel like you're sitting there like a jerk.
你是无辜的
You're the good one.
知道么?
You understand?
你以前有和别人在一起 不停地撒谎过吗
Did you ever go out with someone and just lie...
一句连一句的说谎?
...question after question?
或许是为了让你看起来很酷
Maybe you're trying to make yourself look cool...
或者很厉害什么的
...or better than you are or whatever...
更聪明 更酷
...smarter, cooler...
你就
...and you just...
不一定是说谎
...not really lie...
或许你只是隐瞒些事情
...but maybe you just don't say everything.
这很平常啊
JlM: Well, that's a natural thing.
你知道 两个人出去 出去约会什么的
You know, two people go out on a date or something...
他们想要让别人印象深刻
...they wanna impress people.
让对方
The other person.
或者他们害怕如果毫无保留的话
Or they're scared they might say something...
对方会因此变得不喜欢他
...that will make the other person not like them.
- 谢谢 - 谢谢
- Thank you. - JlM: Thank you.
你以前也这样过么?
So you've done it?
我很少约会的
I don't go out very often.
为什么不?
Why not?
找不到我想约会的女孩子
I never found someone, really, that I think I'd like to go out with.
我打赌你对所有女生都这么说
And I bet you say that to all the girls, huh?
不不不
No. No. Heh.
能答应我一件事么?
- Wanna make a deal with me? - Okay.
我刚说了
What I just said...
大家都不敢毫无保留
...people afraid to say things...
都不敢把一切事情诚实地说出来
...no guts to say the things that are real or something....
- 哦? - 别像这样
- Yeah? - To not do that.
不要再像从前那样了
To not do that that maybe we've done before.
让我们一起承诺:
- Let's make a deal. - Okay.
我把我的一切事情告诉你 你也把一切说给我听
I'll tell you everything, and you tell me everything...
然后或许我们就能摆脱那些 杂碎啊狗屎什么的 阴影啊心结啊什么的
...and maybe we can get through all the piss and shit and lies that kill other people.
哇
Wow.
杂碎 狗屎
Huh. Piss and shit.
什么?
What?
用词很强烈啊
You really use strong language.
不好意思
I'm sorry.
没事啊
No, it's fine. lt's fine.
我不是要 听起来很粗俗是吧 我知道的
I didn't mean- lt seems vulgar or something, I know.
- 没关系的 - 不好意思
- lt's fine. - No, I'm sorry.
真没事儿的 对不起
No, it's nothing. I'm sorry.
我要去一下洗手间 马上回来
I'm gonna run to the bathroom for a minute, maybe, just....
- 好的 - 好
- Okay. - Okay.
- 好好 - 可以?
- Okay. Okay. - Okay?
我现在要进去了 那些狗也在里面么?
I'm gonna go in. And, uh.... Are the dogs in there?
是的 不过都乖乖地坐在窗户边
Yeah, but they stay back by the window.
- 我要你跟我一起进去 然后站在一旁 - 好
- All right, I want you to come in with me. - Okay.
要你进去是预防他有什么情况
And I want you to stay away from me.
因为我是不会帮他的
I want you there in case he needs anything, because I am not gonna help him.
还有 菲尔 别让那些狗靠近我
And, Phil, I will drop- kick the fucking dogs...
- 我会踢它们的 - 好
- ...if they come near me. - Okay.
厄尔
Earl.
你看起来不算太惨啊
You don't look that bad.
狗东西
You prick.
狗日的 你以前最喜欢用这词儿了 对吧?
Cocksucker. That's what you used to like to say, right?
狗日的
Cocksucker.
你自己就是个狗日的 厄尔
But you are. You're a cocksucker, Earl.
很疼吧 是不是?
lt hurts, doesn't it? Huh?
你现在很痛苦了?
You in a lot of pain?
她当时也很痛苦
She was in a lot of pain.
就在最后时刻 她受尽折磨
Right to the end, she was in a lot of pain.
我清楚 因为我在她身旁
I know because I was there, Earl.
你不喜欢 你害怕 对么?
You didn't like illness, though, do you?
我在旁边
I was there.
她等着你的电话
She waited for your call.
等着你来
For you to come.
我不会哭的
I am not gonna cry.
我不会为你哭的!
I am not gonna cry for you.
你这个狗日的 我知道你听得见
You cocksucker, I know you can hear me.
我要让你听见 我恨死你这混蛋了
I want you to know that I hate your fucking guts.
快死吧 混蛋
You can just fucking die, you fuck.
疼死你 折磨死你吧
And I hope it hurts. I fucking hope it hurts.
她心跳只有六下了 快把担架拿过来
Yeah, her resps are down to six. Let's get the gurney over here.
检查自我 摘下来 我是先知
DlXON Check that ego Come off it, I'm a prophet
这位教授 我要去教你的蠕虫
The professor I'm gonna teach you 'bout the worm
最终转向追赶沉船 随着长时间的压迫颈部
Who eventually turned to catch wreck With the neck of a long- time oppressor
他正在从魔鬼那里奔逃 但债务总是增加
And he's running from the devil But the debt is always gaining
而如果他的身价被伤害 他的价值带来的疼痛
And if he's worth being hurt He's worth bringing pain in
说出来感觉很好了么你?
Do you feel better now that you've said this?
我不知道
JlMMY: I don't know.
其实 我没有生气
Well, I'm not mad.
好吧 有一点 但不算 生气
Well, I am, but I'm not.
知道么?
You know?
我太爱你了 露丝
I love you so much, Rose.
我问题还没问完呢
I'm not through asking my questions.
为什么克劳迪娅
Why doesn't Claudia...
不理你 吉姆?
...talk to you, Jimmy?
为什么?
Why?
因为我们
Because we've....
我们都不知道啊 怎么了?
We both don't know. What do you mean?
不 我想你知道的
No, I think you know.
我
Maybe....
不知道
I don't.
说出来 吉米
Say it, Jimmy.
- 我想这样 - 这样
- I wanted to do that. - JlM: Well...
感觉很好 这么做
- That felt good, to do what I wanted to do. - Yeah.
跟你说件事行么?
Can I tell you something?
行啊 当然行
Yeah, of course.
我好担心你听完会讨厌我
I'm really nervous that you're gonna hate me soon.
你什么都知道的话肯定会讨厌我的
You're gonna find stuff out about me, and you're gonna hate me.
不啊 为什么? 你要说什么事?
No. Like what? What do you mean?
你是这么 这么优秀
You have so much, so many good things...
你这么冷静
...and you seem so together.
你是个警官
You're a police officer...
为人正直 什么问题都能解决
...and you seem so straight and put together, without any problems.
- 我今天把枪丢了 - 什么?
- I lost my gun today. - What?
我今天把枪丢了
I lost my gun today...
然后无数人在讥笑我
...and I'm the laughingstock of a lot of people.
我想和你说 想让你知道
I wanted to tell you. I wanted you to know.
一直在想
And it's on my mind.
我真是太笨了
And it makes me look like a fool.
我觉得自己太笨了
And I feel like a fool.
你刚说我们要讲出来
And you asked that we should say things...
把一切都讲出来 毫不隐瞒
...say what we're thinking and not lie about things.
所以我要对你讲 我今天把枪丢了
Well, I can tell you that. This. That I lost my gun today.
我不是个好警察
I'm not a good cop.
我左思右想 我知道
I'm looked down at, and I know that...
我害怕你听完就 就不喜欢我了
...and I'm scared that once you find that out, you might not like me.
- 吉姆 这非常好 - 对不起
- Jim, that was so great. - I'm sorry.
非常棒 你刚才说的
What you just said.
我结婚后就没有约会过了
I haven't been on a date since I was married, and...
那是三年前的事儿了
...that was three years ago.
无论你想对我说什么
Claudia, whatever you wanna tell me...
无论你觉得多么糟糕
...whatever you think might scare me won't.
我都会静静地听的
And I will listen to you.
我会默默地听 如果你想的话
I'll be a good listener to you if that's what you want. You know?
我不会妄加评论的
You know? And I won't judge you.
我有时喜欢这么做 但今天不会的
I know I can do that sometimes, and I won't.
只是听着你
And I can listen.
千万别害怕会吓到我
And you shouldn't be scared of scaring me off...
或者害怕我会怎么想 什么的 总之
...or whatever you think that I think and on and on.
说出来吧 不管是什么 我听着你
Say it, whatever it is, and I'll listen.
- 你不知道我这有多傻! - 没关系
- You don't know how fucking stupid I am. - lt's okay.
- 你想不到我有多变态! - 没事儿的
- You don't know how crazy I am. - lt's okay.
- 我有麻烦 - 我会去面对的
- I got troubles. - I'll take everything at face value.
- 尽管说出来给我听啊 - 我提议做这个的 是吧!?靠!
- I'll be a good listener. - I started this, didn't l? Didn't l? Fuck.
不管是什么 告诉我吧 你可以的
Whatever it is, just say it. You'll see.
要吻我么?
You wanna kiss me, Jim?
是的 要
Yes, I do.
说吧 吉姆
Say it, Jimmy.
我想她觉得
I think she thinks...
她以为我骚扰了她
...that I may have molested her.
她脑袋里老是有这些糟糕的念头
She thinks terrible things that somehow got into her head...
觉得我真的
...that I may have done.
她最后那次告诉我说 那是
She said that to me last time, when it was...
十年前了 她走出门 你不该摸我这里 我知道的
Ten years ago, she walked out the door. You touched me wrong. I know that.
诸如此类的疯话
Some crazy thought in her- ln her head.
你真的这么摸过她么?
Did you ever touch her?
不知道
I don't know.
- 吉姆 - 不知道 我真的不知道
- Jimmy. - I don't know. I really don't.
但你竟然能说出这些!
But you can't say.
- 我不知道那时做了什么 - 做了 你做了!
- Well, I don't know what I've done. - Yes, you do. You do.
- 就是不敢说出来 - 我不知道
- But you won't say. - I don't know.
什么?拜托 别这样
What? What? Please. Please.
活该你该一个人去死!
You deserve to die alone for what you've done.
我真不知道做什么啊
I don't know what I've done.
你知道的!
Yes, you do.
露丝 我说知道的话 你能别走吗?
Rose, if I said that I knew, would you stay?
- 不 - 但我真的不知道做什么啊!
- No. - But I don't know what I've done.
你肯定知道的!
You should know better.
好了 我们约会了 你下次还会想再和我见面吗?
Now that I've met you, would you object to never seeing me again?
- 什么? - 说不想啊
- What? - Just say no.
- 我怎么会不想 等等 克劳迪娅 - 只需要说不
- I won't say no. Wait, Claudia. - Just say no.
- 克劳迪娅 这是什么? - 让我走吧 吉姆
- Claudia, what is it? - Just let me go, Jimmy.
- 这是什么?不要 - 没事的 让我走吧
- What is it? Please, please. - Please. lt's okay. Just let me go.
为什么不打电话?
FRANK Why didn't you call?
我恨死你了
I fucking hate you.
去死吧 畜生
God damn you, fucking asshole.
哦!你这个畜生
Oh, God, you fucking asshole.
别这么走了 畜生 畜生
on't go away, you fucking asshole.
天哪 别死啊 你这个畜生
Oh, God, don't go away, you fucking asshole.
怎么了我这是?
What am I doing?
我做了什么啊? 我他妈的怎么了这是!?
What the fuck am I doing? What the fuck am I doing?
男子是空虚的 看看他们的秃斑 并说：
Men who are vain look at their bald spot and say:
你知道 我不需要什么 我看重我自己的方式
You know, I don't need anything. I look great the way I am.
是的 女士们 如果你希望你的丈夫或男友
Yes. Ladies, if you want your husband or boyfriend to-
哦 操
Oh, fuck.
嗯?
JlM: What?
干什么呢 蠢货?
What are you doing, dummy?
哦 伙计
Oh, brother.
天上在下青蛙!
Oh, there are frogs falling from the sky.
大家都知道 你不是要去花135美元
You all know you're not gonna spend $135 for it.
事实上 你的一生在这里度过 在这个特殊的电视推广
ln fact, all you spend here during this special TV promotion...
只需要39美元
...is just $39-
快! 快点!
JlM: Come on. Come on.
克劳迪娅 是妈妈啊! 快开门 亲爱的!
Claudia, it's Mom! Open the door, honey!
克劳迪娅 你在吗?
Claudia! Claudia, are you there?
妈! 妈!妈! 妈妈!
Mom! Mom! Mom! Mommy!
哦 亲爱的 没事 没事了
Oh, honey. All right. lt's all right.
没事了 会好起来的
lt's okay. lt's gonna be all right.
无奇不有
This happens.
任何事情都有可能发生
This is something that happens.
在回到被绞死的那三位囚犯
And there is the account of the hanging of three men...
和那个业余潜水员
...and a scuba diver...
还有那场自杀
...and a suicide.
无数这样的故事 充满巧合和偶然
There are stories of coincidence and chance...
各种交叉和离奇
...and intersections, and strange things told...
如此这般的故事 谁人又可预料得到?
...and which is which, and who only knows?
而通常我们会说
And we generally say:
那种事也就电影里才有 我才不信呢
Well, if that was in a movie, l wouldn't believe it.
某某如何如何 遇见了某某 诸如此类的故事
Someone's so- and- so met someone else's so- and- so, and so on.
以敝人之见
And it is in the humble opinion of this narrator...
这样的奇闻轶事其实每天都在发生
...that strange things happen all the time.
日子就是过去 一天天过去
And so it goes, and so it goes.
书上说:
And the book says:
虽然时过境迁
We may be through with the past...
但我们不会改变
...but the past ain't through with us.
不好意思 杰克
PHlL: I'm sorry, Jack.
是医院打来的 琳达的事情
lt's the hospital calling about Linda.
- 谁? - 她现在在医院
- Who? - Linda. She's in the hospital...
我觉得既然你在 还是你跟他们谈比较合适
...and I figured you should probably talk to them since you're here.
你好?
Hello?
嗯 那个
Uh- huh. And what-
好的 好
Okay. Okay.
嗯
Uh....
她还好吗?
ls she gonna be all right?
哪里 ?
Where...?
能看到么 琳达? 很好
You with us, Linda? Good.
你是 琳达 对吗?
lt is Linda, isn't it?
放轻松 好
Just relax. That's it.
会好起来的
You'll get through this.
爸
Dad.
爸 你需要对我好一点
Dad, you need to be nicer to me.
睡觉去吧
Go to bed.
你必须今后对我好一点 爸
You have to be nicer to me, Dad.
睡觉去吧
Go to bed.
我知道自己做了件蠢事
I know I did a stupid thing.
太愚蠢了
So stupid.
戴牙箍
Getting braces.
我以为
I thought....
我以为这样他就会爱上我
I thought he would love me.
戴 牙箍
Getting braces.
图什么啊!?
For what?
为了些什么 我都根本
For something I don't even....
我根本连戴到哪颗牙都不知道啊
I don't know where to put things, you know?
我太想爱上一个人了
I really do have love to give.
只是不知道该爱谁
I just don't know where to put it.
大多数人以为我仅仅是在完成工作
A lot of people think this is just a job that you go to.
一顿饭时间 好吧 就完成了
Take a lunch hour. Job's over.
诸如此类的东西
Something like that.
但我把它当成我的人生
JlM: But it's a 24- hour deal.
没有退路
No two ways about it.
而大家都想象不到的是
And what most people don't see...
认认真真做对一件事需要多大的努力
...is just how hard it is to do the right thing.
大家以为 我下个处罚
People think if I make a judgment call...
下个判决就完事儿了 不仅仅是这样的
...that that's a judgment on them, but that is not what I do.
事情不应该就这么着了解的
And that's not what should be done.
我必须负担起一切
I have to take everything...
负责一切的正常运转
...and play as it lays.
有的人需要恩惠
Sometimes people need a little help.
我认识个家伙 很擅长做牙齿矫正手术的
I supposed to be real good at corrective oral surgery.
有的人需要宽恕
JlM: Sometimes people need to be forgiven.
有的人需要惩罚
And sometimes they need to go to jail.
给这人打电话吧 行吗?
Call me about that guy with the teeth, okay?
在我看来 这正是最需深思熟虑的一件事
JlM: And that is a very tricky thing on my part...
下判决
...making that call.
我是说 法律是无情的
I mean, the law is the law...
我当然不能违背法律
...and heck if I'm gonna break it.
但你依然能巧妙地饶恕别人
JlM: You can forgive someone.
嗯 这就是最难之处
Well, that's the tough part.
如何宽恕他?
What can we forgive?
乃是工作中最难之处
Tough part of the job.
乃是我沿街巡逻时最难之处
Tough part of walking down the street.
我来这里
JlM: I just wanted to come here...
我来这里是想对你说
To come here and say something.
一些必须说的话 你说过的
Say something important. Something that you said.
你说过我们得把一切说出来
You said we should say things and do things.
诚诚实实 毫无保留地
Not lie, not keep things back.
别让这些话闷在心里 让自己痛苦
These are the things that tear people up.
好吧 我现在就要说出来了
Well, I'm gonna do that.
照你说的那样 克劳迪娅
I'm gonna do what you said, Claudia.
我不能
I can't let this go.
我不能没有你
I can't let you go.
你 听着
Now, you...
好好听我说
You listen to me now.
你是个好女孩
You're a good person.
你是个美丽的好姑娘
A good, beautiful person...
我是不会让你离开我的
...and I won't let you walk out on me.
而且我决不会再让你说什么
I won't let you say those things.
说什么自己多傻多傻之类的傻话了
Those things about how stupid you are and this and that.
不会再让你这么说的
I won't stand for that.
你愿意的话
You want to be with me...
我们就在一起吧
...then you be with me.
(subtitle from http://shooter.cn by SPlayer2490
怎么样?
You see?
(subtitle from http://shooter.cn by SPlayer